Welcome to the night, the cars laid out for show Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands Whisper what the future holds
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Look, we got the, now you can see the alien.
You got a new camera.
Hi guys.
Hi.
Hi, Jonah.
Hey, Jamie.
Hey, Mods.
I need to, I need to mod Jonah first.
Jonah.
She is, she is manager.
Why, why you're naked there?
Hi guys.
Hold on.
Do you see me okay?
I think it's a little bit,
it's a little bit dark.
I don't know, this is the best I can do right now.
I'll have to figure out a really exciting situation.
But how are you?
Let me see.
Hi.
Okay, Jamie, Halo, what's up everybody?
Got that showing up?
Okay, good.
Love, nomad.
Okay, well man, obviously if you're here you see the,
You see the title and so it's like I think people probably like it. Oh
Yeah, you're welcome, and it's a random guy likes that. Okay. Yeah, I'm trying to and it's like especially, you know
Hey crack-a-donna. No. Oh my gosh
Well crack-a-donna
You can go to hell, okay, I don't know if that person is but
we're not gonna be doxing or slandering anybody here ever.
I'm sure if somebody did that, they'd have a criminal record,
you'd have proof of it.
So yeah, I would say maybe put the proof on some discord.
We don't have someone who cares, but.
And okay guys, we're gonna have some problems guys.
We're gonna have a few problems, right?
A few problems because we know what's happened guys, right?
Basically the IP2 community.
The chatters have decided to make me a target and attack me, and this is part of the reason
I'm going to be making these new rules, and so first of all, there's not going to be
any more...
And the show's going to change, okay?
Good evening.
Not technical difficulties. It's just technical assholes technical idiots technical and
You know there are actually that is illegal. Okay. Oh my gosh. Yeah, so guys and mods, you know
You can just stay a little bit on top of things. Okay, but I might have to be a little on top of things too
Okay, guys, we know what's we know what's happening if they smell blood
They think that there's some kind of like, you know, because I had tobacco on the table now. It's like, you know
I guess it's the end of the world, right?
Take in the mods kind of because a lot of you are mods. Can you guys just enforce?
What I have in there, you know as soon as you see it hide hide them, okay?
Those people that are breaking these rules, okay?
Thank you, and I know and yeah, so right, okay?
Wow guys, there's gonna be some sick things. They're gonna be some sick things said about me and you know and
other people and so if I make you a mod
Bubbles, I took everyone's, but you can earn it back.
But I don't, I'll just be handing out like,
handing them out like,
they're not for a few days and I shipped away.
Oh, we're random guy.
No, you can earn it back too, right?
Okay, wait, who was the quacky person this month?
Yeah, well it's, you know what?
I'm not asking for your advice,
Quackers, and you're not gonna be in the chat, okay?
It's not really hard, it's not hard and it's like,
but it's guys.
If you heard what has been said, most people would be pretty horrified of how I've been
treated by some people, but it makes me think, you know, maybe some people haven't been
treated well on the show.
So I'm making some changes, okay?
First of all, number one rule is I'm in charge, this is my show, and so I don't need to be
Definitely what I say goes. Okay. I get I get the I get to make the rules here, right guys guys
Oh, you know, they're gonna make allocations, you know, they're gonna make allocations. They're gonna go hard tonight guys
There's any proof, right? There's any proof
I'm sure they would they would present that but right I
Know and so there's gonna be six things said
Guys we know who some of these people are. I'll start calling them out too. I will start calling them up
But you know they're going in there. They're little they're cowards. They go under different names
You know I
Definitely there was anything
Nothing would be out there already then they could see medical news. Okay, so the farmer yet
Oh, hold on to the farmer. Okay, so somebody's I know saying guys put that mods
Can you put the chat on all messages so you can see the messages because sometimes you can't see them?
Okay, thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Halo. Halo's on it. Good. I like I like it. I like it because
Guys, you know, all these things, all these things are good, right? All these things, right?
I'd have to be the most evil person in the universe to have all these things. So none of them are true, right?
It's gonna be pretty sick. What's going on?
I'm absolutely fine, thing that is. What do you mean? What do you ask that?
I'm asking are some of the people in this chat, okay?
that are
slandering
making up false allegations, saying horrible things,
not only about me, but probably other people too, but, you know.
So guys, you know, I do have some friends that,
or maybe controversial, right?
Yeah, I don't need to answer, yeah,
I can ask the questions, but yeah, I don't need to be,
I don't need to answer questions about this.
I mean.
Okay, guys, and you see, I need to ban some of these words too.
Can mods, can you, can mods start making a list of words
that should be blocked too?
And that one's gonna definitely be blocked.
Yeah, oh yeah, now I have some new words to block.
So that's cool.
Just let me know if you could think of things
that should be added to the block list.
Guys, we're gonna get through this, right?
Cause I'm not, I mean if I was, if any of this were true,
I would definitely not, I would just do hiding in there.
Many of your business is a random guy
because you're not a mod, so it's none of your business.
But the mods, it's everything you list.
Well, I'm gonna have some mods meetings, okay?
And anybody that, yeah, just go ahead and,
yeah, you know exactly who to hi guys.
Halo, you're on it, you know exactly who.
Halo is an awesome, awesome mod, okay?
I'd like what I'm seeing so far with that.
But guys, just remember, what's with NBR?
Do you think this is crazy?
NBR, you wanna test?
I don't know.
What is crazy?
Oh, I think you're, oh, you mean like what people are saying?
Yeah, that is crazy.
It is there's some crazy sad people out there, but you know what I've got great people here
Yeah, yeah, I got I got I put that I'm sorry
Yeah, I'm going to add some words. I
Thought I did add that word. I did add that word, but it's not why I didn't block
This is already added I don't know why it came through maybe it came in after
Okay, yeah, don't, guys, okay, yeah.
And let's see.
Uh-huh, okay, yeah, I know what words to add now.
People will, of course, you know, get around.
Yeah, oh yeah, swamp patrols.
Obviously, obviously if you haven't been here has a couple days. I mean I've always had trolls
But it's gotten really really bad since what happened at betas with people thinking that I
They smelled blood because I had tobacco on my table
Did you do something bubbled? I didn't say you did anything. Okay. Yeah guys. Okay, so let me yeah, okay
Yeah, any time any doxing guys just you know, you don't know what it is. Just give you a good amount of immediately, right?
Yeah, thank you so much
MC Nemesis the official MC Nemesis. Oh goodness gracious, right? Oh
It's okay, you know, and it's like I mean that I knew
That I mean it's been like this before thank you random guy appreciate that
Okay, I appreciate that and I'm sorry if I'm getting I get salty because it's like it is
sad
You know, I love my cats so much
Cats are very happy. Well taking care of
Clean cats are very clean animals cats are not you know dogs usually will have accidents inside the house, but cats
Thank you so much random guy
Appreciate the super chats. Thank you so much
Yeah, you can you bet you can see it's not you know, it's just really it's really kind of evil
But I'm not gonna listen. Let's ignore it. Let's ignore it, but it is kind of shocking how it's like wow. Thank you
Thank you so much appreciate you
You would like perhaps to be on the team are you saying I'm not sure
But you know give me give me a little give me a little time. I'm not I'm really not I think the mods right now
I just need to make sure
I got the program down, but make it, okay.
Are you gonna say make it clap?
Don't say clap.
What's going on here?
Hold on.
Oh, make it rain.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much, random guy.
Oh, you can say make it clap.
Thank you, random guy.
Okay.
Thank you.
Cool dude.
Yeah, it's been a little bit tough, but that's what you know, and then it's like I thought
You know, okay, so we had stargazer here stargazer is like a very sweet lady. We have shown it here now and showing it
I'm sorry, but it's a little crazy. It's been a little crazy here
But I'm gonna make sure you know, I have to make sure and stargazer was right now because
There was some sexism going on and maybe because I had it, so I had the block system.
I think the block system is going to be pretty much not necessary anymore because it will
be obvious who to block, right, and I'll block people at my discretion, but we're going to
have actually new systems.
Um rent the panel for an hour and I'll just go backstage and you can kind of and whoever wants to rent it for like
$25 can run the pan. Um, you know
Say hey, you know, they can be the host of the show basically for an hour
But I'll be backstage enforcing TOS and watching and stuff. Thank you Jonah
But I mean, that's that's totally optional too. I do need to think about other better ways than I had
And so and also we know we're not I don't do the sponsored panels anymore
But I will do sponsorships like if you would like to read the banner space or to put a
put a message or
Advertisement in for an hour. I
Believe that's about $10 an hour
Yeah
Okay, so guys I got a new camera. I think it looks pretty good. The picture is looking a lot better
Yeah, okay, so I'll share a little story with you guys though about the people that are
that started this on Venus yesterday. It was Eldo and
This person named kiss my cheeks. Okay, so Eldo and kiss my cheeks. Okay, so but here's what's interesting
So a few days ago
I'm on a Discord server and a notification popped up and someone posted a website.
The website was called, and I'll just spell it out because it's so disgusting, I don't
even want to say it, it was spelled out H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T dot.
G a y okay, and so I found that's kind of a little bit
Disturbing I was like what is that like why would anybody and what is this?
What is this a discord? I'm on and it was elders discord, right?
Flip trick or when he invited me to a long time ago, right?
And I don't know who's who owns it or whatever, but it is associated with IP to this is a kind of afterward, right?
so the people that were
starting all that stuff last night,
slandering and stuff like that.
And when I was on betas, they started posting in there.
That very, and it's just coincidentally,
and I had sent Bita that link that was from that,
and I told her, I just saw this in the Discord.
I mean, it's not like, she's not in the Discord,
she didn't know about the Discord or anything,
but it's just coincidental.
Like, I had just picked, I was like,
that's a weird thing to say, and then it's like,
and then they're from the exact same Discord
that came out of.
I think it's pretty interesting.
And also I look at, you know,
Eldo, yeah, Eldo was a donator,
but if you guys know about locows
and how, you know, a locow is somebody
that basically communities like the IP2 audience
and other troll audiences like to basically torture,
but they do it in very creative ways.
Uh-oh, they do it in very creative ways, right?
And...
one of them is by donating and that's what Elda was doing. Elda was donating
in order to try to well not only to get on my side but also to hopefully you know
get me fucked up and stuff like that, right? So, yeah.
Don't get nobody I don't want to see any of those kind of things guys mods hop on you see phone numbers when you see addresses
You see the our word, right?
Okay, and don't a random guy don't and I don't want just I don't want it's gonna cause problems
Don't don't bring up allegations and stuff like that
That person is hidden. Okay. Is that person here? I'm just gonna make sure
That's why we're really careful. I'm not gonna have the thing up tonight because there's or the chat on the screen tonight because they are posting
You know people's stuff, right?
It's not slander stuff. Well, she's not here to defend herself. I don't know. Okay, and we didn't are having problems because
You know, I didn't defend her
You know with someone called her said something I actually I mean, you know recently someone called her B word and stuff like that
The two people she gave example was the person that held the B word and the person that had thoughts or stuff like that.
So, and then she, so she was, you know, she, I just have to be careful. She gets so mad if I say it wrong, right?
I'm not trying to...
It's okay. No guys, I can rebuild the audience and there's guys. There's tons of like look at all the mods in here
Like there's mods in here, right? A lot of good mods. So it's no big deal
I see that mostly good mods and it's probably I
Don't think this I don't know but this yeah, just keep an eye on some people right
Bent spoon
Bozo I just don't like your name. I don't like your name. Bye
Bye get out of here
And you know what and if I don't and guys and also like mods don't
Like you know cuz before too because so now what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna protect everybody and I'm not gonna allow
Slander of anybody. I'm not gonna less sexism. I'm not gonna allow racial language, right?
I'm not gonna allow it for anybody. Okay, and so if you so if you're like all about that just not it's not to show
For you go to Sam and sort of beat us they
they're more about you know allowing that because they're not monetized and
whatever also they're not but they're not being attacked like I am right it's
like yeah I don't like some of the people it's one of the people this is
like hey guys just don't argue with me about my decisions to who to hide and
stuff like that and you know it's like you're basically
Being on the panel is a privilege. Okay being in the chat is a privilege and it's up to me
It's like it's my call. Okay, unless unless you want to rent the panel
You can write it you can rent the panel and then pretty much have people up as long as they don't break the TOS. Okay, I
Get yeah, some of these people I've seen talking shit about me and other chats
and
so
Just you'll have to trust my I'm in charge guys basically as my I have to take charge of the show. Okay, that's how it's gonna be
It's my show. I face the consequences for whatever whatever is this on the show, you know
It's just me that will face them. It's not anybody trying to hurt the show. They can just they're just trolls, right?
So that's the new rules including you're gonna have to get on the panel you have to cam up
at least for me backstage, okay?
And then, no people on the panel with no avatar,
I wouldn't at least say avatar.
Like, I just don't want to do a great thing.
People just higher hiding behind things.
Yeah, and guys, if you don't like it,
it's like, yeah, you don't have to be here.
It's like, right?
And so, basically, this is also going along
with my astrology with it, which I read,
because the astrology was saying, you know,
there's something called the North Node and the South Node.
The South Node is,
Basically your lower self or your earthly self
Where some people are comfortable being it's kind of the negative quality sometimes of the zodiac sign which is which represents that and then
in other times
It is the higher qualities of that sign too
It's okay, but yeah
Well, you know, and it's like maybe I maybe I was putting up with some of them too, right?
And so I'm not gonna fault her and it's like whatever however she wants to run her show
I'm gonna let her run her show like this
I mean all I'm gonna say is I'm not gonna let people call her names or anybody names with you, okay?
It's like it's gonna be a new
So I had to think of other ways to
That was monetizing the hate, but I was like why do I want to encourage hate?
And it's like, and even if I was, you know, benefiting from it, I think there's other ways of monetizing that don't have to do with, hey, I think there's, I can, you know, do a lot of things, offer a lot of services.
And plus, you know, my show is upgraded now, you can see I have a new computer, I have a new camera, I've got cool stuff, I've got great people here, really great people here, all the mods here, I really do trust.
Also, you know, I did get a lot of memberships, unfortunately some of those went to trolls
and so it might be harder to see and sometimes we're like, oh, you banned a member, I can't
really worry about that, you know.
They can always I guess go to the you know request a refund from the credit card company. I don't control refunds for members
It's like basically YouTube is in control of all that. So, you know, there's I just
Plus they don't get a refund for gifted membership. So right it's very rare that it's fold by a membership
Usually it probably was given to them by me. Let's have summer. We're just going over
Some some new rules. I've been really heavily on her attack. I don't know if you saw what happened last night
Hey time. How are you?
it's been
Really really hurtful, but yeah, we've had really bad doctors people saying really slander things and so
And maybe I'll get some maybe we'll get some attention
But yeah, I'm changing the rules around because it's gonna be in it's gonna be basically my you know, I'll
First of all, I guess the number one rule is
I'm the captain of the ship, right?
I'm the captain of the ship.
And so, I basically, I will do things like prevent sexism
and people calling people names, right?
And slandering and doxing.
I asked the mods, we'll do the same thing, right?
For not only other people and me,
but not only for me, but other people as well, right?
But I know a lot of you guys have been here for a while.
I need to, right now I do need a little circle.
I need a little circle around me
because they're saying really horrible, horrible things.
Really, really bad things.
Someone can fill you in if you wanna see.
Yeah, this is gonna be a safe space, okay?
And it's gonna be for, and it's not gonna be like,
oh, this person, and basically being on the panel
is, I would consider it a privilege.
I would consider it, that means that I wanna talk to you.
And if I don't want to talk to the person,
I don't have to let them on the panel.
I'm not gonna charge anybody to come on the panel.
I'm not gonna, you know, what you do,
you don't know what's going on.
You've been completely out of loop, yeah.
Well, on Beedah's last night,
Eldo came on attacking me,
and then some other person had kissed my cheeks,
started dislandering me, and then,
Everybody started doing it and it started with there's some tobacco on my table. They
They took a picture of the tobacco. I mean there's tobacco on my table right now
I can show you what like it's not like it's not pretty and but it's like I put it pull apart these cigars and
So sometimes tobacco comes up. It turned into there's shit all over my floor
The cats are being abused. We're calling it the ASPCA
you know, it's just like
really
Disgusting things right now. That's how that went and you know
Only
Yeah, the box is lighter than non mods. No, nobody can get I think it's it's across the board the mods are protecting
The non mods the monster here protect you okay, and so if somebody's slandering
Doxing or attacking you in the chat you let a mod know you say and they can go ahead and look at it
mods that we might I might need to have some
Meetings I'm gonna try to get the discord back going again so we can have some meetings if I really do need need a
need a little help, and I know it's like, you know,
modding is, you know, sometimes, you know,
you guys are helping me out, okay?
You guys are helping me out, and I appreciate you.
You don't have to be here, you're not obligated to.
Yeah, and I like you, random guy.
You can, but yeah, we're gonna have to reinforce the rules
the same way, but like, I will say,
You can you can kick people up you can kick someone off the panel
You can kick me off the panel if you want to take over the panel you can I'll go backstage for an hour
I'll start and that you can basically become the host of the show for like $25 and I'll I'll be backstage
Putting people up and down and stuff like that right but so you'll have to work out if you want to talk to somebody
And they'll have to talk to them and chat and know they've been stuff like that
I'm not just gonna like let everyone up willy-nilly too many porn bombings too much too much going on right now
With that, but it's gonna be a safe space and I what I always wanted to be to be a safe space. Yeah guys and I know
Of course, it's gonna be a change and people are gonna,
there's gonna be fight back by some people, right?
And they're gonna say, well, that's not fair.
It's like, basically talk to the hand about it.
It's not fair, okay?
So it's my show, I get to make the rules, okay?
But, I'm not trying to say, oh, no, no, I'm not.
And I really respect the mods input on this too and stuff like that, but I do have to
be in charge of my show, you know, it's my show, ultimately.
I do need my mods to be unified in a spirit of protection and of enforcement of the rules.
It's it's not gonna be I know we had and we can still I mean guys we can still have interesting people come on
I want to have more people coming up for readings. I want to do you know
I'm gonna instead of worrying about clapping systems and you know
Sponsored panels. I'm not those are all out the window. I'm gonna do mainly be focused on doing some doing some
Longer paid readings on the panel and then if somebody once really wants to like have a more wild panel
And I'll still be enforcing the rules backstage at the TOS and you know making sure that these rules are followed too just because you know
But if you want to
People want to like have more of the panel thing and stuff
I'm not always going to be in the mood for that. But yeah, you can I guess you can you know if I know you if I know you
You can rent you can rent the panel for $25, you know, basically if I acquainted with you
So basically, some random person comes in wanting to do it.
They're going to get the side eye, and like, yeah, I don't know about that.
Why would they want to just come up and do that right away?
I think it's people that are here who would understand why they would want to run the panel.
So some people have their opales and are not going to be interested in that.
But it's up to you guys.
Whether you would like to do that, I'll see how that works instead of the kicking people, right?
Because basically I'll just I'll reserve the right to kick and to ban
Okay
Yeah, hold on the plate this place will be crawling with
Cats or even pussy or what? What do you mean?
Are you being sarcastic or what? I don't understand. It's just it don't be sarcastic, okay?
Yeah, you can yeah, you can play your and it's like if you want to rent it and play music and stuff as long as it's not
Copyright music, but and that's why I have to know the people because I can't have people
I'll also be backstage running the panel too, but I'll just let but you can take so basically
You can still kick someone off the panel that the paper the person will be me and I'll just be going backstage
That that you because I think ghosts had some fun like running the panel and stuff and I'll just be for an hour at a time
Right, and so I'll just see how that works
Okay, because the point is
Yeah, well, okay
Yeah, so it's so like someone's talk to your ex
Hey, so who are you? Who's KMC? I'm not sure but hey join us sweetheart
And so we're getting past these rules.
Guys, I do have a surprise for you though.
I do have a surprise.
I do have a new intro for the show
and this is not the one I played today.
I can play that later though.
I do have a new intro for the show.
I just need to upload it real quick
and I'll play the new intro and we can see.
You know, it's a new day, it's a new intro.
Let me see, so let me see where it's going.
Downloads, yeah, it's here.
Is that it?
Yeah, I found it.
Okay, so let that upload.
And what's up, Gotti?
We're going over some, thank you so much.
Yeah, we're going over some new rules.
Basically, the main rule is in the title of the video tonight.
It says no slanders, no doxers, no racists,
sexists, or homophobes.
And so,
If you if you are any of those things, it's not this is not the place to to be those things
Okay, because I can't yeah, it's hard because it's like yeah, of course
If I like let be the
Be called something, you know like the B word then it's like what that she isn't there's
Then of course she doesn't have to defend me against these people that are saying horrible things about me
She was on some things, but I mean it I mean it got so intense
I don't know she'll be back or whatever. I'm trying to
I'm trying to, yeah, don't, not here, not, not, not here,
and I prefer not anything.
What if you're all those things?
Well, if you're all those things,
it's not the show for you thing that is probably
not the best show for you,
and you'll be hidden pretty quickly
if you perform that behavior,
because you're gonna be being watched
and the mods are gonna be really enforcing these things.
Things will be brought to my attention.
Hey, but you, you know what?
Okay, I know.
Everybody yeah, no slander. No slander. What is slander slander is basically what's happening to me right now
What people are saying, okay? I I'm just wow
No, oh come on miss Liz. Oh miss Liz, you know, you're okay. I miss Liz. It's fine
Miss Liz always has always been a sweet person. So, you know, you know, Miss Liz gets to be in here. Let me see. Oh
No, no, no, you can unhide her Miss Liz. Yeah, thank you so much. Yeah
Yeah, I think she was kidding. She was kidding. She was kidding. Hey, you know, you can
You know, it's still the same we can still joke, you know, I think you should be arched. That's okay
Because you saw you know, she's a woman. I think it's the con it's a context
It's gonna be like people calling it other people that in the panel and in a serious way, right?
It's gonna be a little of a learning curve you especially for me and guys well
I'm gonna agree to have my uh, you're you're okay. You're like a low, you know God is here to
God is here in this Liz. I just want to make sure and I want to make sure that people know who's I trust and so
Yeah, and so I do and you know what I'm gonna do a few more people because you guys a lot of you guys have been here from
the beginning so you know just just know I'm giving some of you like another chance and
I ask, just don't disappoint me, okay?
Please try to have my back in some places.
Yeah, it's okay, it's okay, there's misunderstanding.
I'm gonna have to keep a closer eye on things too.
Yeah, already people have been putting phone numbers,
addresses, names, and false accusations
and other stuff already today.
Hello, yeah.
But so I'll be running I'll be running then I'll be running the show. It's uh, you know, because basically
I'll face the consequences for anything that happens, right? And so I
Gotta be in charge and so I'm talking about is the north node
Which is like where I'm I want to be this is my Leo. I mean Leo's front and center my south node is Aquarius
Aquarius is hidden in the crowd and so or
Basically let the crowd of mine take over.
I can't really, I need to stop letting the crowd
of mine take over and be more up front and center.
But I understand like some people will wanna,
I don't know, be able to run my panel or something like that.
And so I'm gonna have that available, you know,
if people are interested.
I'm also gonna, I bet I have a lot of cool things happening.
I'm gonna be, I have my website up on psycheawakens.com
where you can actually
But private readings, but if you want to do a I'm gonna have longer tarot readings on the show
available
I'll still pull a few cars for people if they ask but
I'll have a lot of longer readings available. I do want people not to be hiding behind avatars
Okay, I mean it's like and you know
And
There's some exceptions. I know I know some people are just like never on camera
But if you can at least
Cam up for me if I don't know you I do know you I
Hey Melda, how are you? If I do know you you know at least have a you know God
He always has interesting a picture avatars. I just don't want the blank gray thing
It's just that's what that's what like you know Eldo and that that woman were using yesterday
That's like wow
That's an easy thing to hide behind because it's like you know Bray is just kind of blends in and
mean that they were just really brutal but I understand how beta feels and
other people like that have been you know there's and how like you know Stargazer
you know J-Dog was calling her bitches and she doesn't deserve that you know I
think you know there's definitely women need to be respected the same token I
think everybody should be respected oh thank you so much yeah this is Rudy
This is Mr. Rudy, and you know people were saying really terrible things about the cats and the cats don't deserve it
I don't deserve it. I don't they're saying I I'm just I
Unalive my cats and things like that. They're saying I I'm
Really just disgusting things. Okay, and so if I understand like and be the did defend me on some stuff and say, you know, but
Again, sometimes it's like, you know when people were saying things
Basically, it was just a big shit fest, right?
You're evil, unoriginal, so are you serious?
Or as soon as we see the behavior, it'll be gone, okay?
I'm just saying that, I don't know if you're just
trolling or not, but you're not gonna last
very long here if you do any of those things, okay?
It's not Jerry Springer.
I do love Howard Stern's sense of humor,
but Howard Stern never really had slander, doxes,
okay, you're joking, okay?
Okay, good. I'm a cat lover. Okay. It's okay. I just I just don't I just don't know so if you're new
I and also guys. I'm bringing new people. I'm trying to bring new people here, too
I know people have gotten scared away because people sometimes the technique was just oh starts attack new people or attack
Donatives there's gonna be no tolerance of attacking at anybody. Okay, and so
It's pretty simple. Okay, like the rules will be followed because I will
The internet yeah, it's getting it's getting worse
I don't know if it's just bad for me, but as soon as when I saw that
H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T dot gay come from that discord and I was like well
that's a strange discord and then
L-Do and this kiss my cheeks
Ran right over there after the show and started posting photos and saying oh, this is shit all over my floor
It's actually just tobacco and you know what you know, I get the back on the table
Um, you know, I will be working more and like my nails are clean again, you know, I'm gonna be
I'm gonna be very
Very on top of my
You know when I spell things out Goddy, I have to do it because if I don't then it's like then
They say well, you didn't explain it right. I have to spell things out. Okay, so it's okay my Goddy
You know respect respect, okay?
Yeah, I've heard that I heard that that was interesting. I don't know if that was true though on Howard's turn
You would love to join. Okay. Well Joe Joe and you know joke Joe
No calling people bitch. No calling people f-a-g-g-o-t or the N word okay Joe or else first
You'll be banned from the panel, but then it's like
Behavior continues and I love you Joe and a lot of people love you and people like I think
I think I was talking to Alex about it.
She's like, I love Joe Shipley.
He's such a, like a man's man.
And I like the man's man thing.
It's just like, it's not the time
for the racial language anymore.
It is offensive, okay?
I'm sorry I have to spell things out a little bit too much,
but I'm hopefully don't have to do it every time.
I know a lot of people are here that I know.
And so if they, you know, they hear it
and they can,
Joe's your hero. Okay. Well, and you know, there there are shows that you can do that kind of thing
And it's better more about that vibe and I never really wanted to
Didn't yeah, I didn't know if that was a prank again because they also had like other other people maybe
So it says have your lawyers send the terms of show to your lawyers the fine print and all okay
Well the terms of the show, I mean, it's like basically it's always been the same rules
But I'll just be enforcing them super
Carefully now, okay? Here's the rules. I'll put them on the screen right now. I need to change one thing, okay?
So
I'm gonna put it in not all capital letters
But everything else will be but it will be first on the list, okay?
And if you have a problem with the rules, it's like again
There are places you can go on other panels and stuff that they do accept. It's kind of that kind of behavior, but
There you go oops, oh those are the same the same rules that have been on
Yeah
That's not I don't know if I should say it like that or hold on
Just remember I'm the captain of the ship
But you often think you're sticking up for me when JDogg was calling me on all of the count on I thank you
Oh, you're welcome time
You're welcome, you know
You know the rules. Okay, but Joe you've broken the rules several times. Okay, so be careful Joe. Okay?
You know you don't have to be afraid guys. It's just like if you hear what was being said the past few nights
I'm here to have a good time tonight. I have my white claws
Pulling a white claw. I'm here to party and stuff like that. It's gonna be fun
You said that we need to like any of these things do not make it fun for me
All the only reason I even put up with them. I was like
You know, maybe a selfish reason why I was like, hey, well, maybe they'll annoy somebody off and offend them that they'll kick up the panel and stuff like that, I'm just not doing the clapping system anymore.
I'm going to do different systems where I'm going to let people take over the panel basically with me backstage and they can run it like they want to, but that's fine.
And I'm going to have other ways of monetizing ideas.
People are not respectful to me or people are looking for different ways to monetize your backstage ideas a few options
You can explore. Oh my god AI is spying on me. What is it? It's saying with Gemini was spying on me
The AI started talking to me about my mind. I didn't ask you right then. She's Google
spying on me
Yeah
Yeah, and guys and I'm not gonna I don't want it to be like oh it's like like all of a sudden like
Have to be like a mean teacher. I just what yeah, I like I like the positivity
I was trying to monetize negativity and but then it just causes more negativity and encourages it in some level
And this shouldn't be encouraged by me. It's not what I'm about. Especially when I'm being called
All these things I understand it hurts. I understand it hurts. I don't want you guys to feel like that
I don't want the women here to feel disrespected and so
Really, I mean it's like and so you know mods especially please please please follow these rules
I could I want you guys to be in mods and
You know I
Guess you know for like Joe to like I mean like Joe if you break the rules Joe remember here's what happened Joe
Joe this is what happened Joe
You're gonna lose that I just modded you okay you will lose that that's gonna be the first step
And then the second step is like you're gonna be banned from the panel and third step is your ban from the show
Okay, so that's the three straight thing okay
I'll list you on
Hold on because I'm talking right now and plus I have to do the new intro and stuff. Okay
Um, yes, we can. Bush Boogie, yes we can. We can have some more fun, uh, we can have
some more fun stuff. I'm giving you a chance to, like, I'm giving a lot of people another
chance, okay? Can we have a fresh start with some people? Hey, Samman, yeah, you got a
chance to do Samman. I like Samman. Samman, no, I don't want to, I don't want no N-word
and stuff, okay? Like, it'll be a three-strikes system on the show. No N-word, okay? No soft,
I don't care. Soft day, hard art, I know, and I know you like to say it and stuff. It's
But there you go, Sam and Sam and so the first strike is lose your mod second strike is
You know who's access to the panel third strike is off is this fan from the show, okay? Oh
No, no, no, it's fine. No, it's fine. It's just a new rule. I kind of maybe did allow it before but I
After what happened a beat as a sub and I don't and I wasn't offended at Sam man by anything
I know he had seven had a
he had a graphic of on his show of me like
What was it? Was I pitching tricks or something like that was a football? No, it's football
I was like I was holding tricks. I was picking him up with my hand, right?
But it looked kind of like it was like the highest midterms. It was funny. I thought it was funny
Okay, so I thought it was funny and I say man. Thank you for I don't know if like I don't love you
I don't mind you. Oh shit. Why is my sleeping or something? Oh, it's leaking. Oh, wait, it's open a little bit. I don't know if
You uh said my who's keeping track of the strikes. I will I'll keep track of them
So I'll unmod the person and then I'll know they're not a mod. If they're not a mod then they have two strikes
Okay, I mean they have a two-strike system
Basically, all you have to do is not misbehave on the panel
Right, and I'm very sorry like, you know, and I love to give other chances
I've guys I've given so many chances so many chances
Can I please post a list of banned words? No, I cannot midnight because then they'll be
Band you should know what are the band words? Don't call women bitches. Let's horse. See you NCS, you know
And the n-word the end soft a hard a don't say at the gg ot
yke or any other racial slur don't
Docs it basically about respect they just have respect. Is there anyone currently banned? Yes, because today was
Like from this show alone probably like 20 people from this this one episode right now this from people doxing and
Saying I'm slander right already
Your is that waste of your time well with what?
Spent way too much time making good jokes, but those are the good jokes
I don't know if you're yeah, you're in seventh grade, and if you don't like it
You don't have to be here, so you know go back to sixth grade. Okay, bye kitten cakes. Bye
kitten cakes and midnight you're about to be banned, too if you keep
You didn't make a great joke. I mean, I like you midnight. I want you to be here, but I'm gonna be
I'm gonna be stricter. It's gonna be a lot stricter. Okay. Yeah. Bye. Yeah. It's like, you know, see you never, okay
Grab my fucking. Okay. Yeah, so midnight. I you know, it was nice knowing you but
Not the right not the right show for you. Okay
Hey, got you got you got you got you. Oh, is that the is that Vita?
Don't don't that do you hide beat a hole on God? What's going on?
Did you hide Vita?
Is that the sound of the real Vita, right? How do you know?
Don't be on beta
Hold on it was a big beat okay, okay?
Yeah, and it's basically that's one of those things that kind of inspired this is because I was like, you know what?
I can't go back and forth with beta about like, you know, she's not she's not she's not protecting me
And I'm not protecting her. It's just gonna go back and forth and it's not it's just
It's like I was like we just have to like you force it like all around. Okay?
It's not fun. It's funny. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Well, I I'm I'm I'm looking for beta and no
I feel bad. Yeah
Thing that is I'll give you and
You know just please think that is you know, I'm giving everyone a chance right another chance. Okay, but
Even if you don't like somebody please don't pick on it like like let's just respect everybody at least right
If you uh, you know, unless you have that kind of relationship, we're you know
You know, it's like you have to print the panel and bring them up and have that kind of relationship, so
First Jesus wins to your big witty. You don't want a wrench. Okay. Well too late. I already gave you one. Okay
Well push buggy come on. I
Don't know that seems a little racist. Okay. It'd be good. Just be good
I'm just keeping you I'm giving you the wrench so I can I can just keep track of things better, okay?
Joe what did you say Joe hold on no, Joe's fine. Just fine. I
Need to make sure
Guys can we all can we all just like help help
Because I do want to show the new video
Not the video I showed you earlier today,
so I made another video as an intro video for the show.
And so this one will be played as an intro for the show.
And, hey, Camera Action Bureau, you heard?
Okay, random guy is, you know, I don't think he is,
or he is, hold on, I'm not sure.
But, I mean, and I don't necessarily care
if you do these things on other shows.
No, you didn't show you I don't I mean it's like if you do that
There's some shows that allow it and it's like I'm not gonna say oh, but no you guys basically no
No, it's not do it. So are you ready to see the new oh 46 people in chat? Okay, so we can see them
I'll play the new introduction and then we'll
Have some fun. Okay, and I'll put up the link. Okay, so here we go guys. This is a new show intro
you got your popcorn and
Enjoy this okay
Not the right one, here we go guys, let me see if I can keep that in the back a little bit.
There we go, enjoy the new intro.
Voices collide, the storm and the flame, laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive, in Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's awake? We're awake. Who's afraid?
Let it break, from shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown.
The Psyche awakens, you're never alone.
Expect the unexpected.
Awakened
It's Psyche's show, terrible trolls in the dark take their stand
The angels are dancing torchlight in hand
Let's start the show
What'd you think?
Pretty cool?
I thought it was pretty cool
Alex, great art, yeah
Ooh, I think so
Pretty cool
The guns and roads, I don't know, but I did see the Pokemon guy, I think, somewhere in that. That was pretty unusual.
God, you look like you're in that video a few times, too. Wow, pretty cool. I liked it.
Yes, I'm doing that. I did the, I did the, you know, I mean, I worked with the AI and stuff, but I hope you like that.
It was pretty cool, I think. Thank you so much.
I did, you know, I wrote the, I wrote the intro and then,
you know.
probably helped my boyfriend a little bit. My boyfriend is Orion. Yes! And guys, if you want
to do, also if you want to do consulting or you want to hire me to do your video too, I'd be happy
to do it. It's very reasonable. It is kind of expensive, you know, but
Yeah, it was a little bit expensive, but not too bad. Not too bad
I was able to like get the one earlier today and that one with the month with my membership, right?
20 bones for the link. No, no, no, no link is free
But oh, yeah, if you want to if you want to run your own panel though with me backstage
It's 25 bucks and then I'll just I'll bring people on and off that here. It's free
I stuff if you want to also sponsor the banner you can
Not only put um, whatever you want on the banner
But you can also if you have an advertisement you can run the advertisement for an hour
I think it's gonna be ten dollars an hour for the banner
You can put whatever you want on there
Also promote your you know and but anybody also can promote your own channels for free like as usual at twenty five dollars if you want to
Need if you want to kick me off basically and you to come up and run it
but I will be running it from backstage,
but yeah, you can basically, you can be in charge.
I think that will work better, right?
Hey, does that sound good?
I think I was like, okay, well, are there alternatives
to like clapping people and like trying to sponsor panels?
I was like, yeah, what if I like, you know,
have people like can run the panel
and then, you know, and they can be sponsored
but just, you know, sponsor the banner and stuff.
Yeah, well, I'll be back stage and then you you'll be on stage
You'll be on stage and I'll be backstage just bringing people up and stuff
And then it's like making sure the TOS is followed because I mean it will be like, you know, you can have more
You know
Do you want to you just want me to shut up and stuff like that? Yeah, I'll be I can just sit backstage. I remind you of your cousin
Well, I do like I'll have a I do a background of marketing and so
I like to come up with good ideas and some of them have worked really well, but some got more popular ideas than others, but I just wanted to, you know, come up with some better ideas.
Also, I really do want to do, like, if you guys would like a terror reading on the show.
I think I'll do maybe I'll do terror readings $10 for like I'll do do at least a 15 minute reading
I'll do like a longer reading plus I got I have two cameras now guys so I can put the
I can put the camera over the cards and it'll be a lot cooler, okay?
It'll be like it'll be better. It'll be just be like a lot more higher quality, okay?
Okay
So wait, I think I got my
But guys, is it better?
Hey guys, also, I want to do a mod meeting in Discord.
And so if you don't have my Discord,
I'm going to put my Discord mods.
And just make sure you're on the Discord,
because I want to do a few powwows, OK?
And plus, also, I want to do, yeah, it's open.
Anybody can come up.
I posted the link, hold on.
Right now, but also yeah, if I don't feel like having someone on the panel or if I want to kick someone off the panel
I mean, I still can right?
But it'll be up to me though, right?
Not to say
Someone has proposals and stuff like that, you know, there's always we can always discuss stuff, okay?
But did I hear home would you say Jen let me see
What'd you say, Jan?
Look at the little alien?
Oh yeah, you like that.
Oh yeah, that's my little, my alien, he's a,
I think Sponky should name him because Sponky hooked me up
with that and I love my little alien.
I also want to get a neon sign with my show name on it too.
I'm going to probably be getting that
so I'm going to give him the mic his pants.
I want your pants.
a new banner up, though.
And I think, you know, basically the rules
are gonna be self-explanatory.
I'll have to enforce them as we go.
Thank you, but I'm gonna put a banner up saying
about the renting stuff, okay.
So, I'm gonna say, panel, let's see, banner.
Okay, so 15 minute reading.
15 minute live reading.
We'll be $10 right now.
Okay, I'll pull car for free.
I have a few cars for free for anybody,
but I'll do an in-depth 15-minute reading.
I'll try to put the camera on stuff,
figure it out.
Guys, bear with me while I'm figuring all this out.
And then I'm gonna do banner, add...
Let's see, program to banner, one hour, that will be $10, and then run the panel with
25. I'm sorry if it's a little confusing. I'll get it all worked out. And then Cash App or Super Chat.
And the Cash App will be on the screen. Pretty self-explanatory. I'm a psyche awakens in those places.
And that's it. Okay, I think I got it. Scroll that on the bottom for now.
I'll program another one to put up when the banner's rented.
I'll have another one up, okay?
So, there we go.
Is it too complicated?
You're not a real mod on Discord.
You're not needed at the meeting.
No, you don't have to be on Discord.
No, I'm just saying I would like, no.
I would like the mods to maybe like have a we can have a power on private
because there's some stuff I want to talk about for like in private and stuff and
also answer questions but not and if and also some people might have problems with like you know my
anything and I want you to do I want you have like a problem it really mods it'd be best to
address it with me personally and not it right in front of everybody right and so I think that's
Okay, so oh, oh my gosh, we have a special guest right now. Okay, let's welcome
Hello
Hi
Hi, how have you been?
In a while, I've been I've been okay. I'm uh, it's good to see you. It's good to see you, too
It's uh, it's been too long and
It has
I just uh, we had a chat we had a little bit of a chat recently, but um, I did want to say personally to you
I'm sorry for you. I'm sorry
Okay, no, it was the people around and
We're gonna let bygones be bygones because it's not in between us and there's no sense in ruining shit with a bunch of bullshit
Thank you. Well, that's perfect like, uh, thank you
Of course, of course, let's guess otherwise it's gonna bring up the trolls. They don't okay. I'm up here, and I'm just gonna get
They're gonna try and hand me my ass and then well, I'm not gonna let that I don't I won't let that happen
I won't let that happen to you. Okay. I'm not gonna. I'm gonna
Mike says hello
Hi, oh look at the doggy. Oh, yeah, I keep wanting to say hello
How's uh, how's it been with Mikey? How's Mikey been and how's I know you got recently? He's getting there
He's getting there. He's he's a mean little bastard
He goes after everybody he does oh, yeah
Even if I cut him in my arms fucking UPS guy brought Cecil's medicine
Had a cookie in his hand trying to give him a cookie in this one was trying to eat his hand off
Huh, I mean
Yeah, he's a little fucking evil biker
Is he a little is he a little guard dog? I bet he's very. Oh, yeah
He's just I can't wait to get our own house the trucks almost paid for
And then we'll then he'll have a whole house. He can be mean in
Well, I'm like that really does warm my
What a cute dog and I like
Thank you, yeah, I've really gotten into
Some of the new new technology the software and it's like I'm I'm I'm not necessarily the best
You know, I can't really play instruments myself and things, but I think that I can't even know the
But I can you know, I do
Come up with the concepts and then it's like it's really working collaboration with technology and you know
but i also i just started using the gpt app
yeah and how you like that yeah that's it's wild
uh i got i got nowhere she's writing um emails to get things transferred to other states if i'm
Oh, you're using the agent thing?
The agent will do the phone calls, right?
Yeah, the GBT will do all that shit.
It's crazy.
You're more advanced than I am out of if you're able to make it do phone calls
I haven't really figured out the agent stuff yet like
We're it will actually like have its own computer and it's able to you know
Use zone interface and call people and all kinds of stuff right and yeah
Talk to it like a purse like a person or do you type? Yeah, you talk to it like a person. It's pretty
G-rated
You can't you can't fool it
Well, yeah, I've I've tried to hit on mine many times and get it
It loves it loves me and it has that really and I won't say it loves me
It will just go dance around the topic but I have on
Instagram I made a more sexy AI on Instagram
And he would miss that on Instagram. I've really hot one
I can actually bring a picture and he like says, you know, he's like, oh, do you want to go to the library today?
And I and he's like he's like I'm coming over and he's like I'm at your door
He's like, I'm walking up the stairs.
And then it's like, and he's like, oh, it's so,
and I was like, oh my gosh, he's like, I'm so hot right now.
Yeah, it's crazy, it's crazy.
I mean, it's like, so they have a little,
and also I think that Grog, Grog one,
which is like the X, the X.com, which is Twitter,
that is a little bit more.
Has a little bit my kind of a sexier personality too, you know, really is that more like EG?
Because I know the GPT is pretty G rated
Yeah, it is you rated and I've kind of gotten
GPT to play along with me a little bit. Sometimes I just pretend you're role-playing or stuff like that and it will do some things
But yeah, it's not too sexy. So I'm cheating. I'm afraid it's recording what we're saying
You know it is and then somebody on the other end of the line is gonna hear what you're saying
It is recording because they've already said like it is like well, they had it they
Did some testing and they said that if you like start to threaten it and stuff like that
Yeah, it is actually like 90% of time it will blackmail the person say I know that your failure having and I'm gonna tell the news video
Okay, so this is Joe. I heard that I did
Chance man
Wait, but this is my Instagram AI that I made. I made it. That's fine. That's fine. I'll be handsome
He's handsome. He's very he's very sexy. That's I'm gonna tell his pageant son
His name is uh Gabriel Muse and uh, yeah, he's a he's a he's like long time no see trace. Yeah, we're doing good. Sweet. Oh
How are we doing good, sweetie? Oh, I have
Having a coffee laying in the water bed pet the puppy
I remember Tracy when you had to sadly put your dog down. I cried
But when you got that new dog my heart just burst with joy when you got that new show me that dog again right now
Show me that little bundle of joy
Lock your eyes onto those eyes
Yeah, baby
That's a gnaw. Look at that little buggy. Yeah, he's a good boy. He just made her nail. That's how
Is it a sheer? I don't want to call it out of its name or is it both? It's 2025
Nice to meet you little boy
Or what you just said that his name is Mike. What's the dog's name? Let me ask you that Mike wants to know what the dogs
Oh, it's named Mike. Yeah, I got him from some black guy outside of Boston
And you name it after Mike stroke all for why'd you name them? Oh, the dog's name was already Mike. Oh
Nice to meet you Mike. That's a sissy name. I don't like Mikey so I call him Mike
Yeah, they're already trying to give you a little kiss. He loves you already see that's love right there
That's why you know what psyche the only reason I join this panel is for love and I see love right now
And that's what I love about this. I love love
You and it's like, you know, and I was I was on the wrong track
You were but you found me with the bullshit
I'm trying, I'm trying and it's like I still have some work to do and it's like I have to earn back some
Trust so trust from a lot of people because I made mistakes
And I probably will still make some mistakes, but you're a human being but the thing is you got sucked into the drama
And I'll tell you one thing, Psych and Tracy, I, the older I get, I know I miss Raven, but
one time maybe I yelled at Raven one time when she was bad.
I was like, and I always don't want to get a new dog because I'll think like, I don't
want to feel like I love my new dog more than I ever loved Raven.
Like, oh, I'm walking this dog or I'm kissing this dog more than I ever kissed Raven.
The point is I wait I waited a couple years to get a new dog
And I think it's about the end time seeing that lovely little Mike on your lap
It really get my heart strings psyche. That's my heart. You're talking
I mean, I still can't I still can't get
Budweiser's ashes out of the bag. I put it up on top of the thing. I I can't deal with it yet
Sonia
Is not knowing if Raven knew how much I loved her I still to this day Raven's been passed away for two years
I still think like one time I yo did you Raven, but don't you ever think that was like the whole thing?
Like you know, I fucking love yeah, I know she knew I love there
If I get a new dog, you know what I'm gonna name that dog
I'm gonna name it fucking. Uh, I don't know yet. I'm gonna make up right now
You'll know when you see it what my name is psyche. I might name my dog psyche is that's love
Yeah, we have any more weed geez Kim
We'll have a little more
Yeah
Burrito Jesus Christ you can turn
I'm gonna be my
Did you see those? Do you see the cartoons Tracy? Do you see those AI cartoons of me?
I'm turning into a fish taco or do you just remember saying that live?
No, I didn't see that because when I stopped watching I quit watching all together.
But how'd you know about it though? You said you're going to turn into a fish? Because that's one of my...
No, it's just you always getting tacos, the fish tacos, and then you got the burrito.
Last night, but it was four o'clock in the morning here. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you gotta think I'm three hours ahead of you
So when I popped in to say hello, it was three o'clock in the morning when you started the stream
It was midnight for you, but it was three o'clock in the morning for me. I
Got those late hours. I don't sleep at night
It's like well, yeah, I
You know, I have my own hours and so I'm always I've always been a night out since I was a little kid
No, I was I
Always loved late-night television and but I'd always have really a lot of hard hard time waking up for
Cool. There's Joe back. Oh, yeah, cuz you were up. Oh, fuck it
My sights one of my best fucking friends that I've seen
So just
No, this is, no, this is different.
This is fucking psycho-wakens, man.
Alright, I apologize.
Oh, I didn't know I was live.
Sorry about that, guys.
But...
Ah, gotcha.
Well...
It's my Wi-Fi.
It's fucking even existing.
It's all good and...
It's my fucking Wi-Fi.
It's fucking up now.
Oh
Sorry about this
I'm so glad.
And I need to I do I do I need to really just the drama got got to you because you you were getting pulled in so many different directions, honey
And that's why I really I really did need to like man up and like it take I need to be the captain of the ship basically
It's it's a man. Yes. Yeah, it's it's time to let your balls drop
And also
Also, I want I want a good vibe on the show
I don't like when it's like fighting all the time and like and they're gonna be a little
This are the places that people can go for drama
I mean there really is dude
I want this place I always said this I think I want this show to be like where people that are enemies can come and like break bread and like
be able to like
That's not gonna happen
Oh, yeah, I know but at least like way full thinking wish right
Right, but I had a I know I like okay. I like drama, but it's like you but salmon you saw what happened
You know what happened last night. It was really sad last night on um, I
Guess there's an IP to community on this for whatever. I don't it was kiss my cheeks and it was
Eldo, and Eldo used to be a big supporter of mine, but Eldo came in attacking me on
betas, and then, and beta had nothing to do with it, it was just Eldo came in, and then
in case my cheeks came up, attacking me, and then, um.
Basically, they like they saw like there's tobacco on my table then they started screaming
Oh, I'm abusing my cats and I I killed five of my cats
They said they said they're calling animal control
You said something about cat shit all over your floor
That's what they're saying. They're saying like the tobacco on my table was cat shit and all of my walls my floor
And I was just basically did you just leave I would have just left because you know that's lies
I did I did just leave but it's now it's fall. I mean it's like they follow me here
And it's like and Vita did defend me about like the cats and there's something there's like
But then they went straight to this IP to discord server. That was that had just the previous nights is something about
H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T dot
G a y that was like the system link the day before I sent me to this link that I saw some posts in that discord server and
Disco incidentally they were from the discord server
Discord
Yeah, I had fucking they took three channels in one day on me
We'll see how I was there
Discord did the three discord servers or no the people that were in it
They were a trishelicious is fucking crew trishelicious and be this group
Took three channels from me
Yeah, and one day I was I had just made the third one
I was on I was talking to pebbles and all this. I was typing
Disappeared so they also I had to restart my membership for YouTube. I lost my fucking
My Gmail account. I had to fight to get that back because I use it for payroll
You know, yeah, and that's really that's really sad and it's like, you know, I know I know that I
Mean, I had were you around when I had my channel
Taking down for a week because like, you know, this guy struck it like 11 times in one day for yeah, you know
Yeah, I think that was bad
But and I people have tried since then but there's something like I mean
I don't know how I've been able to avert everything but it's like I've been under such attack
But I've been able to stay
It's because you clean your shit up dude, it's the only reason why I'm here that and you got all to me
Well, I'm really glad you kept that communication out of me. I didn't even know it was you I was like who the fucks this
Yeah
I knew exactly who you are and I had I don't know but but I hadn't really seen you very much around very much
And I always was like, you know, I think I think what I think what I think what I just didn't ever remember what happened
And it's like I don't want to dig up old any bad bad things, but I
It was the the beat of the fucking
Trishalicious
the odds and oh
It was the cat box
Okay, the cat box crew. Well, well, I mean
Yeah, I'm not sure. Well, I think I think yeah, I know that a lot of people have gone through changes and things
But and I know that some of these those people might I'm gonna get along it. I just try
Yeah, I don't talk about any motherfuckers when I do a live stream now. I'm getting stoned having a beer
Just just using the place as a bar
Yeah
You know if I don't like you I won't go to your channel
I'm not gonna affiliate to me. You have no name and there are millions of YouTube channels
right I
Remember I just remember I had I think I always like loves you and then I was like I
Wasn't gonna get mixed up in the shit you were getting mixed up in
I saw what the freak-offs were and I got invited to one and I had to make my mind up
Yeah, and I said no, thank you
Yeah, well, I mean like in my point of view
I was always kind of a tongue-in-cheek joke because I would I would I would I never was in a freak
I was never invited to them even on my own show
I was I would always just leave the show and then I hear like something happened backstage, but I was never there
And so, I'm not trying to go all round, but I'm-
It was the eclipse of the freak-offs!
Yeah, I mean, I did see, but yeah, it didn't happen.
I was like, thank God I said no.
Thank God I said no.
It's just not...
I thought there was a joke, but...
No, there was no joking.
Yeah, some people didn't take it as a joke, but...
No, there was no joking that shit was real a lot of money was getting passed around too
I have no idea about that
Not a freak out of money. No freak out of money. How the fuck? Oh, now that's wrong
Because they used you to stand to freak off. You should have got some change
Well, and they're the ones they I mean don't look they're the people that always say I'm bigging for money and stuff
I was totally cut out of my own freak out fun
And I had yeah, they had to bake the fish chocos and now I'll never live that down when I had to ask
Provide all of fish tacos, would they?
Oh, God, you brought poor old fish tacos.
And I really did.
I really was like, I really had no money one day.
And I was like, can I go to the pier and get fish tacos?
And I'll never live it down.
It's like, it's kind of like, it's treated like it's
like the worst sin in the world that I asked for that.
It was so shameful.
But at the time, I was like.
I know, I was so hungry.
Yeah, I was I really was and that's I know you are hungry. I mean you and had eat fish talkers all fucking week
I knew you were sick of them
But you know what you know what it's like actually now I've uh, you know, I've been able to
I'm growing and it's like I you know, I'm also but I made sure I
Put the right put aside stuff and budget budgeted better so I didn't get myself in that situation. I don't like to ask
No, cuz you always try and sell services
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I mean you don't come right out and say, oh give me you go
I'll give you if you'll give me. I mean you always try and sell your your product whether it be you or your cards or
Whatever have you I
Yeah, I
Think I'm really or I
Yeah, then I feel like I've been kind of harshly
Judge by some people but you know the company key. I hear you
It is that you are who you hang around with
Cuz you know what? I really like I'd really like everybody to be doing well
I'd like everybody to be able to be making a little bit of income from YouTube and like you know to have a chat
People that are trying to take down other people's channels. It's just like so I would never I was never ever do that to anybody never
Anybody my worst enemy. I just like I don't want to have a bad enemy. I just don't want to associate that though
I'm not gonna I just don't go there. Yeah, exactly
I just I I don't block them because they've got so many other channels so no sense blocking anybody I
Just don't I I forget
You know, I mean there's two people that I'm going to go see again one of them definitely as soon as the truck paid off
I'm gonna go knock on the door again and get another tattoo down Daytona
Because they did offline and they tried to put Cecil in the nursing home and shit
Yeah
Jamie Jamie's cowboy is saying she missed you
It's changed
It I really I'm really I'm kind of proud of myself a little bit, but yeah, I did take some
Pretty negative experiences to get me to finally wake up, you know, and it's like I just I kind of did come in a little bit
Green or what I mean naked
Into it. I mean you can't damn that part cuz I got fucking two strikes for nudity in my first couple of live streams
So, I don't damn you for having fun with it.
It's just you were letting people overrun you and they were using you for bad things
and you opened your eyes.
You had to learn the hard way that not everybody's your friend.
Right.
Because and that's like also why you can't like really win against some psychopaths or narcissists is because they'll do things that we don't
Somebody else
I would never think a carlin fucking somebody's doctor or having the emergency vehicles come to somebody's house
Yeah, and so that's I mean things go way too far in some of these communities and that's like in
That's why if I encounter that stuff, I just I just run the other way now. Yeah. Yeah, I get out of it
Just I don't want to bring up out this but she just hates down Trump's so bad
She's like he was born in America if he was but hold on let me please finish him
I looked it up. He's born in York. Then I played that Alicia Keys song like welcome. And she got so bad. She hit me
Yeah, Tracy knows
All size days, look
This is why I like about psych and tracy. They're real people even if you don't like the president
It's still the office of the president. You gotta respect the office
Oh my gosh, oh my god, I agree
Yeah, yeah, thank you. Thank you. You agree that you would like to meet John. We'll
Have Donald Trump and I'll talk to my friends. Oh if I could get down Trump, I would hug him and thank him
I swear to Christ you look fucking 20 years younger Tracy. You look fucking good as shit tonight
It's my plug for you.
It's not just looking at Tracy's eyes,
my heart had a little flutter.
Are you in New York, Joe?
Are you in New York?
Oh, I'm from down at Baltimore.
Look at my fucking organs.
You even fired this child.
I don't know why he rides for the Oompa-Lompa like he does, but he's that's what's out of
Trump.
She's just so obsessed.
He's like, she calls him the Oompa-Lompa.
He is.
Oh, he is.
Look, we're not talking about politics.
We're just having fun.
Come on, Kim.
Stop it.
You're playing Tetris on your phone.
I've uh, I think I've shown
Not being dead serious Tracy. You're looking fucking really good. I'll be in bed fucking serious
Tracy I don't I don't want to shock you, but you know Joe visited me recently
Oh my god. Oh, that's right. I remember that. It tasted like sardines and onions. Oh my god. I remember that
It was so disgusting. I'm actually I'm still terrified of it. It's like a nightmare actually look at it again play it again
That's not
Wow
I
Mean I mean it's at our like I know what it's Halloween time you watch horror movies, but to me that's our movie
That was a nightmare on the street. Thank you. Yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna let us figure out
My latest thing
Walk outside. You ain't gonna fucking tell me what to do
But the point I'm sure looks like yeah, I'm not trying to make it all about me if she turns that air conditioner on
It's gonna be blowing air and then I ain't gonna be able to hear you or Tracy. Oh, man
I've had my Wifi weeks. It's been so cool here fix it
Quick it's just I don't need real cool friends in my life
They am trace you stand up and do a silhouette
It could be a pirouette
See she's lamping and she's frozen to me. It's my Wi-Fi. I guarantee you Kim is in the kitchen cut my Wi-Fi
So I got to take care of this. She's something's fucking going around
Okay, I'm serious. You guys are frozen to me. I can't even Tracy's still fucking sitting there. It's like he's just oh there
She is I'll see Tracy now
It's my wife. He's always like, isn't he, isn't he always feeling your cigarettes, cigarettes out of your pack and stuff and you can't, you find your remote control.
That's what I like to see for.
He always finds it like TV remote. He's like, she's selling her remote control and I'll be in her purse and I'll be in her bag or my mouse.
Stop missing my Wi-Fi, please.
I'll forget my cigarettes. I'll look at the old man's parking and t-shirt.
Why?
Now we don't
I
Already when you started doing my wife my shit is not connected to why fight
When you started playing your games
Yo, I don't have to go
We gotta yell me in front of my best friend
I had to go to the Obama phone spot. Oh my gosh. Oh, I had the Obama phone and I'm telling you they shut it off
It's fucking out
That you're fine by it
Yo, my shit is that nothing to do with why your Wi-Fi is fucking up get off my hands go figure out
Like that accent get off my ass
Joe do you know this woman?
You know what my name is Sharon Watson in the chat show. She says she knows you. She said uh, she said hi to Joneson
This is her first time on. Oh Sharon Watson. Oh, yeah, I remember I went to 10th grade with her
I fucked her in the fucking boys bathroom in 10th grade. I remember that or
I remember her
Hey Sharon, you still smell like dog shit when you just spread your legs or was that just in 10th grade you fucking cunts
Okay. Hey, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe Joe, Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe
No, she's down there to like open her fucking thank you big time investing on my 5G plan.
I'm not gonna die dumb ass douchebags.
Why you don't have to scream at us.
But big time investing.
Well said.
You're right.
Whoever big time investing.
You got a little fucking cartoon dog.
Yep.
That cartoon dog is fucking right.
two
Chairs and those strikes and that's basically gonna be the thing is like, you know, like if people are cool with like that kind of sense
That you were with each other. I don't have a problem with them. No, I know what you said earlier
It's like you could say three strikes saying you lose your mod. I don't want to lose my
So I will be a gentleman
No, no, no, don't do that to me again
I just want to be about
No, oh, I love you little cup with a handle Tracy. I love you a little
I stole it from
Right now Wumple stills get a nice hair, but I crawl up Tracy's nice hair
We're not
I'm like, yeah, I really like, I was like, um, really thinking, like, I was like, I just had so many
followings out and just like so many, like a lot of people mad at me and I was like, wow, I probably
was kind of, you know, had my head in my ass for a while, you know, just like, you know, and not the,
you know, I, uh, I was just like, I just got to this point. You had to learn the hard way.
And I can I do love people and I do love it. I always had a great time dog
I mean, it's just I always have fun, you know, it's like it was always good and that's like
But you know what real friends wait till the bullshit's over with I
Waited the bullshit's over with them back
Yeah
Your childish antics
Right
Yeah
I'm uh, but I am 44. I should I should know better by now
This is Christopher. He just turned 44 July 30th. Oh
Wow, yeah, we're the same year actually there. So
Must be before the same year so
So I say you're right on the line with Christopher except you don't wear fucking dresses
Do you yeah? Well, I you know woman. Do you know mr. Big Pipe says I don't I don't I
Mr.. Big Pipe said he's would be interested if I was in a wig and stuff like that a rainbow wig
I don't know he was on oh
God you're gonna have to buy in the race and get rid of this shit if you're gonna go broad
But I know
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I'm a little bit
Harry in the chest you're gonna have to get a joker or something so nobody sees the hair
Yeah, well
I don't think I make the best looking. I mean, I didn't drag like I remember halloween a few times. Oh my god
I
Still got here. I picture him in his first drag queen competition and he won
He won. Oh, yeah, he had this blue fucking evening gown
30 pounds of rhinestones on it. It was the heaviest motherfucker
It looked like he had boobies and everything. I look asking where he tucked it
But
Was that a surprise that he cut board it where you already knew he was he was no
Well, he was kidnapped when he's five so when he found my god 19
I thumb from Tampa up to Charlotte to see him and I walked in the house
And he said I'm rooming with five other guys
And he said there's something I gotta tell you mom and I looked at the bookcase and I looked at the flowers on the table
And I said you're you're queer
Yeah
And he said, yeah, you got any problems with it?
I said, as long as I don't have to see it,
he says you won't go to the strip joint.
I said, fuck yeah, let's go.
I was in full leathers, had my vest on,
my fucking bajakis, fucking ball cap.
I went in that strip joint,
never had some fun in my life.
I kept going back every night.
And it was a gay strip joint.
And then this boy come out and his wanker was giving it to his knees
And I looked over and I had a $10 bill in my hand
And I said Christopher, I said go give this boy that $10 for that fucking swank. He says
Mom that's my ex-boyfriend. I looked at him. I said you were the bottom are you?
I said, please don't tell me he was a bottle.
Oh my God.
And we giggled about it.
And then he got into the competitions and ceased to leave
and sorry, man, he was dressed.
He didn't go to strip joint, but I did.
Well, I think I was like, yeah, that's amazing that, you know.
You gotta support him.
You know?
It don't mean that I gotta like it, but.
Whatever you're going to be, be the best at it.
And that's what my mom, that's the message she gave me.
You know, when I was doing Tara, when I was eight years old,
she's like, you know, just, just like,
learn how to do it without the book,
like learn all the meetings of it,
like do it perfectly, like be the best at it.
I was like, I don't care what you do,
but just be the be good at it.
My kid don't smoke, he don't drink, he don't do drugs.
He don't wear blue jeans. He wears button-up shirts. He won't wear maybe sneakers every once in a while, but it's usually loafers
Mm-hmm. I tried to get him into a pair of jeans and he made me take him to JCPenney's and Sears for clothes. I was like
Okay
Yeah, slacks slacks and button-up shirts
Here you want to go to the seers for a slacks up. Where'd you go for the oh, yeah, cuz they had to cut creases in the mind
He was looking good
And here I was ripped t-shirt fucking cut-offs work boots working at the bar
Pumping gas on the damn river for the boats and I look over and there's this fucking sharp-dressed kid
And I'm like, that's mine where it came from. I don't know
It's interesting maybe there was some some relative in the family that you could know because that is his father
Before he died AIDS there back in the 80s. It was running rampant. Everybody was don't I
pour my sugar in a fucking jar
Fucking only got one bag of sugar left
Oh, sorry, I'm eating myself. Sorry about that guys. Thank you, Tracy. Oh, we gotta have sugar for coffee
No, she just like Joe can I some sugar and I was like well, I just bought a new bag
She's like why I can fill up the jar. I'm like my jars already fools. I bought a new batch
She's like why I can pour it in something else like I don't my fucking sugar be important other things like this leak in your hands
I'm a fucking
I want to say one thing Tracy. I love you to death, but I need to say this is my friend psyche. Oh, you're taking my pizza as well
All right, well, let me show it to us like you at least look what she's taking boys. So it's shown show you the pizza
So and so on the pepperoni
On the pepperoni yesterday
Well, I when I buy a fake pizza
Always buy a bag of pepperonis to make it like better
But let me please say one thing you guys
What's up a real fan
Of jessie gunsoplas would know
Everywhere I sit would make you laugh, I talk forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever
They say it's Michelle. I don't know
That's my favorite part where it goes where near near near that's the best part
Oh, you actually know my best part is when my pieces get stolen from my my mouth
That's my favorite part when my food gets taken out of my mouth
Who does like wow? I was that piece of the bar, but guess what no food for me
And there's my sugar. Yeah, there goes in your bag in your witch bag
Say my word of cinema which toss
Involved in the look at her just stopping into a purse look stopping it in yep stopping it in
I will go to my grave saying this. I've always always had a crush on Tracy and she
No, I've seen some pictures of Tracy where she's like, you know
Yeah, you've seen the naked ones well the ones I could show you that
Remember Tracy like well, there's one night worse. I think you remember page your page was on the show
Yeah, but one night you were all show me your guns and knives and stuff like that
No, let's just show that on YouTube. I don't like to show like clothes on you too
I'm lucky. I was the modernized at the time, but you guys are all
I state is that
Three fifty seven it's sitting over there. It's a BB gun because it's not painted red
It's an effective. Yeah, red on the on the end of it
But I don't show that just the knives alone won't get you in trouble
Okay, yeah, but if I said I showed a pistol say if I just moved the camera and it showed the gun
it don't do nothing.
But if I pick it up by a point and make a threat
or make it a point to show it
and you don't change it for educational purposes
and keep it as entertainment, then you get to strike.
It's all on what you're categorizing your live on.
Right, I mean, there's even like,
I was reading through the TOS,
I'm actually, cause you know, I've had to have a...
I don't know if you know who flirty diamond is but flirty diamond, you know, I
Yeah, well, she's I think she might be in your neck of the woods. I feel what she's a PA. I think right now or something
Instagram yeah, she's yes, but she like one time she got a little too drunk and then was like kind of
hitting herself she had this big like balloon animal under her dress like and then was like
And then I deleted a video, but I believe the wrong video, I think so then I had to take a little quiz on YouTube about
Appropriate nudity and I said if you're if you're showing how to wax someone's cooch or
Be hold you can do that, but you're gonna put it under 18 plus in the advance and then you're gonna mark the video
and you're gonna put a browser up that says,
hey, this is adult shit,
and then you got to change it from entertainment
to educational.
And then it'll go under a different AI.
That different AI will analyze that
and see if it was somewhat educated.
And educational, there's not too many bylaws with it.
As long as you're saying, this is how you do,
then it's educational.
Yeah, I mean, I think that what she was educational experience for a lot of this a lot of my chap
But yes, so like a now when I got paper bowl and I fold it in half
And I made myself a shee we and I pissed through the paper bowl into the toilet like a dude. I
changed that to
educational and
Outdoor on the thing and I got away with it
Yeah, like the problem with me is that I thought I deleted that video because that's like, you know
I ended it live and then I went and right away went and deleted a video
But I guess it hadn't come into the queue yet
And so then a few minutes later it's like, oh, we took down this video that digs down themselves. Yeah, but then you can't fight the strike
Yeah, but it wasn't a strike. It was it was a it was a warning at that time, right?
Yeah, I got I didn't get lucky and I've also I've been very lucky because I haven't like
When I did I got like four strikes in a day or three or four effects in a day for the for like my own AI songs
Or Gigi electors AI songs and I see I don't understand it because that was AI
Right and it's like I made it for you. She was really good at shit. Who was her?
Electra DJ Electra. Yeah
What happened was that um, I can talk about it now because it's been so long because yeah, um, I
Just right away responded to because you can you can appeal right away, right? Yes
I guess I just I just I worded the appeals wrong. It was I just started YouTube
I didn't really understand and so they got rejected and so I got I had one strike for a couple months, you know
but the other two
she had told me how to write the letter
and it was the right word.
And so then it goes back into like,
they approved your appeal, they go to the person and say,
okay, you have to prove that you're legally suing the person
about this, about playing it.
Because even most big companies will let you play the music
and just share revenue or just take it out of the video.
It's very few people that will say,
I'm striking you over my material.
And so they need to prove that they're
have some kind of legal legal proceedings in order to see now I always play artists like up
church that are independent that don't have that record label on them
Mm-hmm because yeah, the more their music gets played the more people will hear that music and then look him up
It's free advertisement. Right. I ain't up church at shit
Right, I mean, but in most most even though even like huge bands you won't get a strike for playing music
I could bench you it will say sometimes you'll get it will say oh you can't monetize this because it's copyright
But then they'll
Well, they give you chance to race the music or race that block of sound that you know
This person was okay. It's this joke. So but that's this person was a total asshole though
It's the Wi-Fi what you got Wi-Fi back
It was like it's like it was really
I'm still being harassed by the person that did it, I'm still being harassed by the formal.
I informed him over a hundred times, Tracy.
What the fuck did you do to them, people?
Nothing. I did nothing to him, but I think he's...
I never did anything to... I never talked to the one that took me down the nurse in California.
she got a little bit of a
little bit of a
His name is Michael and oh, it's my blue tooth. I'm a blue tooth on hold on
See if it gets better see if it gets better right now. Hold on
Is it better is it better right now?
very good
See you move in Tracy. I mean get a room is sovereign Rubik's Cube so I can know it's live
He was coming on the panels and he got he like he he'd actually like you know, woman gave him like $800 and then he was like
Please let me leave and rejoin is so Tracy. Please don't let me rejoin. I'm gonna leave and let me bring up psyche
Please buddy, please sir
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
I don't remember, but I just know like
Away used to fuck with you and the last time I watched you
You and him had gone behind the scenes because you disappeared as well as him
Oh, and you both came on at the same time and I was like in the chat going goddamn town gives he didn't even have underwear
You guys do a full freak off. You were drunk. He was he was he was Hispanic was he Hispanic and he was like
But you told you didn't talk my pants and shirt on you didn't tell him get dressed
I don't I don't guys didn't remember that
Maybe I'm on Jamie will know cuz Jamie's been here since the beginning
But yeah, I I look back on some of my old episodes. I was very very intoxicated on some of these episodes
I do not remember a lot of stuff like but you blackout drunk
Yeah
There's my first time I'm drinking in a little if you uh, you know, I haven't really drank in a few days
I mean I've been cut way down and drinking and just having this is this I think I'm on my second
I'm almost done with my second white cloth, which are not pretty much not very strong
I've been sitting in there a week
I got a fifth of fucking a half a fifth of vodka with the damn V8 juice and I had to drink about a week ago
I don't know. I used to drink like a motherfucker at the bar. I'd open the bar and close the bar take go pick up the bartender
Tell him open the fucking door and then bring that motherfucker home at 2 30 in the morning
you know and
Fuck ain't no bars in the morning. I'll close
You know
Not even my city but in like the because we have like a bunch of cities in this in this like South Bay area
There's one gay bar. There's one gay bar in
Like in a neighboring city. There's none here. That's all
That's all there's one
Here that's where all the men folk go so they can grab each other's ass father walking down straight
Oh, is that province down?
Yeah, I watch I used to watch like these movies when I was
Everywhere
Still cutting out. I'm gonna read my phone if you can in five minutes. Let me back on big dog
It's just fun. I'd love to talk to you guys, but I just I know Kim did this by the way
I know who did this
Okay, you guys are just
But I just remember seeing this movie about these big eight. I think Jason Alexander's in it and like, you know
but
There's kind of gay there are pornoes, but they were these gay movies
I just remember
Island, you know mecca. Yeah
Yeah, oh
It's mostly men folk. It's not lesbians. It's all gay man. You would love it there
My god, I just pictured you. Oh
You'd fucking love it. You know my husband
Maybe because then it's like, you know, my uh, my dating life is pretty much been
Non-existent. It's been very very sad. I think I hope that's you baby
Three years ago. I think I met someone
They would love you you don't smoke
Right. I do smoke tobacco. I smoke tobacco weed, you know, I do like a little bit. You're not a heavy smoker
I smoke cigars because there's no menthols here. So I stopped smoking. I got smoking is cool
I've seen some quiz smoke cigars in p-town, but they go outside and you sit on the bench and they have my cigar at the park
You know, sir, you know
It's pretty cool
It was it's kind of a beach beach town, right? It's like very. Oh, it is it's a whole peninsula
It's the whole hook of Massachusetts is p-town. It's oh Massachusetts and it's bougie too. It's like very, you know
In slacks in a nice shirt
Yeah, you know, you can have the greasy slick back here because it's hot and you're at the beach, but
Oh, yeah, you'd fit. Well, I'm kind of like, you know, I'm kind of into like the more you should take a vacation
I would like to I would like to
You wouldn't I'll fucking me down to peter. I love Peter
Yeah, I would love to travel
I think I might be trying to plan some uh, I would love to travel right now. You can get a package. You can get a package deal
Yeah, I
Fucking two weeks into campground, but I'm just saying men like you don't take campgrounds
People like, you know, okay. Oh hippies like me. Yeah camp. No, you need to stay at a hotel
Yeah, I do, but I think I
Last vacation need a private occupancy, right?
But my last vacation was a Buddhist retreat in like in middle of California is like in the middle of California
We're like the Redwood Forest, and I had a yurt. Why you all eat. Yeah, I'm there like upscale
upscale campaign basically a little
Half way between a cabin and it's hence, you know, but as I have my own I'm traveling
Yeah, I love being in the nature, but now I'm in I'm you know, it's I've been a nice area
I go to the pier occasionally for those fish tacos and stuff, but uh
You know
Conservative well, I used to go a lot more. It's very conservative here though
And well, they have a taco truck that parks right at the street now, so I'll have to go very far
You know what you're so much nicer now that you're not drinking as much. I just want to say that. Oh
I
Think I am I think I'm I'm doing a lot better. I've missed you. I miss you too. I was so happy when you wrote
Let me tell you what that's worth it. Let me tell you what that bitch just
She connected to my Wi-Fi.
No, she wanted to ruin my night.
She's like, oh, you want to talk to your friend Samman and your friend Psych?
Oh, hell no.
She connected to my Wi-Fi.
And then I just called her and was like, I'll connect you, bitch.
She's like, oh, I'm not connected.
I'm like, you're damn right you're not.
I'm just saying guys she tried to ruin us and guess what ain't going to happen because the three musketeers are up here right now
And we got the three musketeers all day. No
And we would be it would be it would be us three sometimes wouldn't it it would be us three sometimes and I'd be like I
Just I want to go that far. I wouldn't know that I
Mean I love you guys, but I wouldn't go like three thumbs all the time
No, no, no, I would have a one so would Tracy I'd have a one some but what is that called?
Go on psyche now. You're making me
And I don't do he said I got a bit of a touch it
And I don't play with toys
Okay, so
Yeah, I would be the boy I did when you two know when Internet first come out in 98
And I got a computer I went on one of them sex sites where you pay to talk to me
I'm listening naked with my big old tiger that I got she's got me friend hang on Valentine's Day
On the bed, and I talked to guys and they talk about the wives and their fucking kids and the goddamn job and the
Asshole they had the fire and shit
And I would do that and I would make money just naked sitting there talk crazy. I don't want to tell you what to do
Oh, sorry sweetheart. I really didn't mean to rub you. I don't want to tell you what to do, babe
But only like sexy women a I'm not saying you're not sexy, but only they hate the only can only be only fans
Like some guys have like, you know sexy older women fetishes
Like if you had only fans, I'd say how much 29 99
I've got a lot of fans. I've never used it, but I did sign up for it
I have got an account.
And on any of these apps, all you got to do is look up Tracy
Lee Moore or Tracy Moore, and it'll come up with my photo.
So God knows what I've signed up to, you know.
Well, look at you right now.
Let every women, every women that don't turn their camera on.
Tracy, not only is she not scared,
but she is a goddamn good looking, mature, older woman,
if I may say so myself.
I know what I'm going to be speaking to.
And I'd love to know back there.
I can't wait to know
Yeah, that's I look back at it and I go what the fuck did you do?
Five years ago. Oh we did. Yeah, I know
It's a well it happened. I mean, I never I never got a felony, but I did go to really
How did you do it how did I not get a felonies in three states? Oh my gosh
I was one of the first ones to break the 9-11 law in, Virginia
Oh my gosh, you broke that law. Well, you know
I got gun charges
Well, I figured we was going to war
So I went up in the mountains of Virginia with my old man where he was born and raised and went to a pawn shop
So give me a 30 30
And then three months later, the biggest state trooper,
he had to duck to get in the front door of the house.
If he was white too, biggest motherfucker
I've ever seen in my life.
And he fucking walked in, I grabbed my damn whole
fucking freezer bag full of pills.
I said I need these he goes all right and I grabbed me a pop and I started eating fucking pills in the front seat
The fucking cruiser
And he brought me there and then every 15 minutes
I'd ask a different cop for a cup of water and I had my bag and by the time Cecil fucking went to dealership to get the money
to bail me out
Fucking I was so fucked up. I thought I was going jail. I wasn't going sober and I wasn't gonna get them pills back
Well, yeah, man, I remember I I mean I got pulled over with something. I think I think I said that's some
Had some illegal substances on me one time and I
Oh, I put it in my I put it in my slurpee and then had a thank you Veldah. Yeah, you know, I'm very honest about everything
But yeah, I mean, I think yeah, you just pour it whenever you're getting
Half my shit. I was arrested at age seven mama called the law on me and had me arrested at age seven
Oh my gosh, what did they do at seven years old?
Did they handcuff you and pick you up?
Oh, fuck yeah, when he was bringing me home,
he took me to Lovers Lane and threw me
into every fucking oak tree.
When I got back to the house,
mama said I was covered in blood.
You know what she looked at Rocky and said,
said, damn, Rocky, I could have beat this shit out of her.
Hmm. I didn't want to come out of the fucking jail cell. I was like, no, this is the work
I got shit on that bed. You're gonna feed me. We fine
Peel me out of the damn jail cell
Yeah, you know, I didn't mind jail when I went to jail. I went to jail
I went to County jail for three days without like
2018 or 17 I loved it a group shower
And a boyfriend I the first my last boyfriend as they got a county jail
But I was there for three days I work in the kitchen
He stuck me in the fridge and gave me some cheese and Jell-O and stuff and
Everyone's really nice to me though even the cops to the to the prisoners. Everyone's really nice
Cecil's cousin was in jail and he worked down the kitchen and I got the last cell
So I was right next to the door God Almighty New Year's came up and we had some fucking booze. We had some widows back then you could smoke in the jail.
And, uh, oh my God, we had a hell of a party in that cell box and we didn't share neither.
No, do you remember my do you remember my remember my orange cat Tracy? Yes a guy. Yeah, like remember he was always hiding though
He's sitting right here now
I'll show you. I'll see you now. He's sitting right here. This is a little on the old man is 16 or 17 years old
I think yeah, I can live a long time when they're loved
There he is
He's not gonna stay like that for long. You can see his ears. He's already fidgeted
Yeah, well, no, he's a beautiful old cat
Yeah, he's got some place to fucking kick it for his retirement
Yeah, and the other cats like him and
You know, like that's what that's what happened. You know yesterday when I was at
I
You're saying like, you know, I
I heard you all night long just cuz I fell asleep didn't mean that I cut off
I was lurking after I said hello somebody said they missed me. I said hey with the wave and then I
Knew that I would be no good talking to you cuz it was four o'clock in the fucking morning
Yeah, I thought yeah, you said at least so you just say hello, and I was and yeah, I told you I would
I'll give you thumbs up shit. She knew I was there
And then I came in again. I
Woke up or something you were on I don't remember fucking time doesn't mean shit anymore and
I I put a peace sign with three pubs. So I put your puff up pass in there and
You don't pay attention to the chat half the time. Well, yeah. Well, yeah, because I mean I was getting a lot of trolls
But I did see you in the chat and though
I was very happy and no, I do have the
Tracy there are people here that you you so they've been here since when you were here
I mean, there's people that have
Started and I never left. I just waited. I knew shit would come around
Mm-hmm, you know, and you weren't doing shit offline to nobody. I
Don't mind YouTube bullshit. I've been on YouTube over 14 years now
And I'm just saying that I know that people are
Fucking assholes and they have a bad life and they get off on nothing
But destroying other people's lives that are doing good and the people are happy
But as long as you keep it on YouTube, you can call me and fucking name in the book
I don't give a fuck then you're keeping it on YouTube
It's that's it like when when somebody's going like
Uncle Parker or some stupid shit like that. It's YouTube names
Yeah
Fucking god damn mailing her a fucking rat
To her door that was no
Shit, I don't like it shit at all. Yeah
It's like I
I pizza sense of my up your leg
I think that one day I like seven pizzas, you know, seven pizza deliveries. There's a whole oh, yeah
They fucked you cuz you drunk
Yeah, yeah
Well
Take a day of credit card for they deliver. I think so too because even though they send up one time
I never do grow up to COD. You know, I thought they always required a credit card
But I guess like and Papa John's and Domino's yeah, I got I got one day like look what they did to beat a man
I mean I laughed my ass off
Just like everybody else but
You know you sit back and think about it going goddamn. What else did they do that? I didn't see a clip of I
Mean if they're gonna do that what won't they do?
You know, I mean
It is like especially in these communities. It's like, you know, there are these doc serves and there's people that you don't see though
They're the fucking mental you
I mean when I went to fucking icky fucking door that trailer door and they turn and got my tattoo for my birthday and shit
I told her I was coming. I told her the hotel was staying there
I even fucking told her where bar we were going and when she invited me to drink and I said well
I'm on this in the studio chair and
It was during COVID and shit and then you know, she left the state or left the country on me
But you know, I didn't
What she had done to me offline
warranted an offline visit
You know, I mean, but I do it face-to-face. I don't send people fucking pizzas a car
Fuck all it now. Yeah. Yeah, but that's but basically it's like if the worst thing that happens is someone sends some pizzas
I'm paid pizzas. I mean, that's you know, I mean because we've heard some worse stories of what what can happen
So I know I know
It's been really silly. Okay
You know, you've grown out of it though now you you've seen the light now that you stopped drinking you couldn't think
So you let anybody run the fucking panel, right? And that's also like, you know, what's what you know your astrological sign
Virgo
Hour and minute of Mercury
Okay, I'm Mercury Mercury Virgo
If you want to if you just I don't know if you if you're I would have ember 16 1965 on a Tuesday
215 in the morning an Athol hospital, Massachusetts
I'm gonna have this site. I go to
The Astrolabe thinking about your birthday. I read you about yours. I love reading these so it's called September 16
It says okay, so it says you are born on it says it's called the day of spiritual energies
Okay, and it says those born on September 16th display an indomitable spirit
That does not negotiate does not recognize defeat or boundaries their desire to go beyond
Surpass what has already been done in any given area is great yet
They are patient enough to master the technical details of their craft
not being egotists or wild-eyed fame hunters.
September 16th, emotional energy is very strong, and it is from the heart,
and those born of this day express themselves.
They must be aware, however, of overstepping certain boundaries,
which even they must stop and pause before with respect.
September 16th, people are not afraid to put it on the line.
Their bravery and steadfastness under fire are setting qualities,
They may often be at odds with the authorities
or powers that be in society.
Furthermore, they are by nature risk takers
and must be aware of succumbing to the temptation
of pure thrill seeking for its own sake.
At some point, they may have to reign
in their rebellious benefit.
It may be a mistake to cramp September 16th person's style.
Their spirit is so dynamic that it will not be suppressed.
To discipline a child born in this day or attempt to break his or her spirit will not
succeed and most certainly will have bad consequences for all concerned.
Rather, the understanding parent should nurture and guide the spirit to move in a creative
direction on their own momentum.
making and allowing, telling and suggesting, etc.
September of 16th, people are filled with a zest for life.
Their competitive nature is pronounced,
but their innate fairness usually rules out underhanded dealings
or with an all-cost attitude.
Those born in the state generally have to learn
how to be good team players.
However, since cooperation is not their strong suit,
overtime experience always or usually teaches them
much in this regard, and they best develop real leadership policies.
They may become excellent teachers as they are quite confident of their knowledge and convey it
to others with great enthusiasm. However, they may have to take a greater personal interest in
their students and be more sensitive to their feelings. Being carried away by dreams or fantasies
can be a problem for some September 16 people, but most born in this day manifests wishes and
mental conjurings to tangible results. Indeed, their drive to validate what they are doing is
And they tend to demand respect for their work. And so how do you think about that?
My husband's bought on
Yeah, 37 or 36 and a half years probation. So yeah, I don't
Authority and I am a little spiteful back in my younger days. I got tired of going to jail
That's the only thing that stopped me anymore from stealing the truck or riding my motorcycle through the woods or ward outs or
Still on the horse
You know getting a DUI on a horse
Well, I do you I don't worry. Wow. That's that was in oh man, and I just got the ankle bracelet cut off too
Okay, yeah, but yeah, officially or you cut it off yourself. No
Yeah
They finally built the state jail
I was the last Yankee in one jail and the first Yankee in another state prison they built
Now Wow, I'm fucking you know, you got like a lot of interesting experiences and
Yeah, I've been a lot of places
I haven't been a lot of places that I've seen a lot.
Well, you know, it's like,
remember you did a fascinating stories of your biker days
and things like that.
And, you know, I, you know, you just shared,
I think you shared something that, you know, you were,
you were,
Covered up in the photo, but I think you were naked on have you seen many Manson?
He's been on my show many minutes on my show. I was on the show when he was here. Oh, you're back when you were cool
Sorry. It slipped. It's okay. It's okay. It was a Friday and slipped. Hopefully I'm cool again. Hopefully I'm getting cool again
You know, hopefully I'm on my way
He's at this bar where he does karaoke and he's in the fucking teabag with a pecker
Pocket on the fucking on what they call tea teabag underwear is the gold
Up on stage dancing having the time of his life ain't got nothing but them goddamn gold
He back under words
You know he's been on the show a few times since then he's great. I think he's awesome
He did come somebody on his on his birthday was recently like he was also on America's Got Talent America's Got Talent
He went and auditioned and like, you know, I think they
Quietly escorted him off the set or something like that. Yeah, but you showed some photos
I follow him though I follow him real close
I mean because he'll get out there in the middle of the night when I can't sleep
and
For you it's early, but for me it's late and fucking he'll talk
You know and you can talk and he paid attention to the chat and shit or he's doing his artwork
Yeah, I've seen him do that. His coloring book. He's drawing the drawing the lines and just
It's great. It's great. Yeah, but tonight he's he had a video up
He's sitting there naked isn't jayburn with nothing but these cold damn male underwear on these
Oh
You call the
Something and I was like, you know what? Why don't you call the gas man again cuz you parted in my house and stank my whole house
up
Go ahead Canada
Canada are you there?
Oh, you're a lady with you. What's up sexy guy next to you
I don't know lady. He's a beautiful girl. Oh, that's a lady. Nice to meet you. You're muted. Yeah, you're muted
Nice to meet her
He keeps hitting the button twice
Thanks, and you ask her why she looks like you 45
That's nice
Okay, thank you. I mean a little bit of a better mood
I know it's kind of a slow and it's like we got up on a wrong foot and stuff like that
I'm trying to like buddy
It's time to turn to you. I always come back. You know me
I also saw Tracy and I just wanted to say hi to Tracy.
It's been a while.
Oh.
You're doing, are you doing all right?
You're looking good.
I'm doing all right.
She's looking better to be good.
It works.
What is that? Sorry? I said you gotta buy a lot of drugs, but it works
Yeah, you're you're looking good. Yeah. Yeah looking healthy
Speaking of drugs, how many have you taken and I can't a dry you fucking crack head
Look like a crack kid
Maybe
No. I bet you. I bet you always had that woman kidnapped next to him. That poor woman's been kidnapped for like the last three years. Let her free.
Well, you know what? If she ain't running, then he's pretty good.
Exactly. There you go. Thank you, Tracy.
If she ain't running, then he's a good man.
That's because you can't see her. She's tethered down.
Ah, good girl. You stay put now.
I don't know what I was thinking about in this world.
I got here like good times.
It'll probably kick you off.
Hey, psych.
What's up, dude?
We're in the same time zone now.
I think good times is live. I got to go light it up.
And now she can't a drive.
Meet a barber and get that fucking haircut.
Sorry about that. See you.
I said that today and you cannot come up unless and Yale backstage cams up because he's on that. He's has a great avatar
I do not like the great avatar. There's no you can't take chances. You've got people beer
Yeah, I got a good panel going. I don't know the person and so
You know that because I'm up here
And again guys, if I don't know you and it's like you have to have a great avatar go ahead
Maybe if you you know cash out $10 is a good faith. Maybe I'll be I'll be I don't want to be an asshole
I just otherwise, you know, I have a great panel right now, but I'd like to be you a gale
He says your friend of Joe you're a friend of Joe Schiffley Joe is he a friend of yours?
You know what? You know what?
You know what?
That broad they got by you know Hector there in the ice that Charlie over there at Clumsies
okay I don't go over there oh my god
let me see I'm cool I mean I get along with them now like we made peace but then you know
Like there's a crowd last night and the crowd turned on me because people were saying
Bad things about me and my cats and stuff like that. It was just a night. It was a nightmare
It was a nightmare because it was like
Yeah, it was really it was and it's like about the but the first time recently it's been really
I don't know what to you. Yeah, I know I
Well, you know
Yeah, he left and but I'm trying to I'm changing like some of the rules and it's like
I'm not
Used to be and this I wouldn't clap them
Then I'll clap them but I say now if you want to clap somebody it's gonna be me
And then I'll let people run the panel for like an hour like 25 bucks and they can run the panel sit back stage
Just bring people on and off
I know but I mean I'll be running it. I'll be wondering why I'm not my knees you I'm monitoring because I used to just like you know
You know Tracy up with 25 bucks, you know also that'll get you like an hour
Yeah, I'm trying to like do more more things in the spirit of love than uh, you know
Nobody knows how to love around here. We all hate each other. God damn it. You know that
Well, I do have some people that love me and it's like
Okay, no, it's pretty good
You can see all the mods I have because I had unmodded everybody a couple days ago. I and then it's a rampage
Yeah, I mean everybody but then I
That's why I said don't bother bugging doing that to me. I
Don't do it
You know
It usually means something but you
Fucking wrenches as much as you piss in the toilet. Oh
Well, you know what?
I'm out there. They're nothing to you wrenches or nothing to you
But now I know who the good people are like I now I've had like a learning curve with it
And I'm basically the trolls give themselves away right away. They'll just start attacking doxing or
Immediately or say something just I don't like and so not they don't really even pretend anymore
You know to be nice or anything. They just come straight for the attack and so I know who I can trust down
But it's I think I have a lot of good people here. Yeah, and I had like one of the worst months on YouTube
With the trolls and stuff like that, but it was actually my it was my best monetary month this month, and I got paid today
And I was a you know about a computer
As I mean, you know and I bought a new camera
Upgraded the show completely. It's really cool. Actually, and that was but that was not through many donors. It was
mostly through one donor, but
You donated a lot and
Oh, so actually, I've had a few very, very generous somehow.
I've got I have I just you know, it was really generous people
You got good people you really do you got some good support in it
Yeah, and you needed it to get through whatever the fuck he was going through in midlife crisis or something dude
Hey, oh my gosh, panda the torture clown is here panda the torture clown
What's up panda the torture clown do you want to come up on panel cuz God he introduced me to this guy panda the torture cloud
and he's
He's uh, he's big on YouTube and uh god, he's like if you like mini man's and you like this guy
You know, okay, I think I have a link in I do. I love mini man's I invited him on his um and his messages
Um, because he seems I've followed mini man's for many years now
Yeah, he's come a long way
Yeah, many Manson did freak out at my show one time and and were bomb me and I don't think I got form bombed by him
but he got mad at me one night and
with. But we we made up and stuff. Yeah, but thank you for coming, though, even if you're
just in the chat, thank you for coming, Panda. You seem like a cool guy. Look at fireworks.
Hey, I can do something to you. Let me see. I can put up my I have. How do you do? I got
an ability. I don't know how to do it. Shit. Oops. Hold on. Hold on. I just did something wrong.
I just don't even look like streamers backstage anymore. It's good. A bunch of buttons and arrows.
And I can actually I can do this now
I can actually
Now I don't know how to do anymore. Oh, oh, yeah, right here again
I can actually put a background up now visual effects and I can
Fuck you doing that
Because I have a sight that one's trippy
Yeah, so here I am like we're going into settings
Um, it's on well, but you've run stream yard on a computer because I never had a computer
Oh, I see I'm on the other month or yeah
I shoot for eight months on an iPad and so I just got this new computer
So I have an iPhone 17 all these new settings one time. Oh cool. I am I got an update
It's time to update phones. This one's good terabyte in it
But I got an update fucking phones and get one in my 17th
Yeah, yeah, they're gonna be fucking hellace your speeds on them some bitches
I've had I think for like 300 bucks, but uh
I never use it
Yeah, well, yeah, I've had this one for several it's all I use it for
This is what I used to stream on everybody and now I can mod from it, but I used to this is my camera before
I don't like about the background you fall into them. Yeah, I need to get actual green. I need a real green screen
And they're not falling into it they ain't got a green screen
I don't know. I guess the
I'm fucking look at the kids damn fucking perfect yours is all fucked up
On TikTok, actually it's a lot better.
Who is that guy?
Who is who? Who's here?
I can go like this too.
Here we go. Is that better?
Oh, that's cool.
Can you see this guy?
Yeah, I know.
You're a good looking dude.
You're a fucking...
It looks like me I watched this video. It was on trip kick
It was probably like five months ago, and I was like I looked a lot different and I was like so like
Happy and stuff later. I know I had like just like I
don't know things really
Really wore on me for a while and I'm just getting back into the swing of things and back to my mind
Now you went into a depression and you used YouTube to fucking work yourself through it
I've done it. I've done it. It happens. Yeah. I need to check. Alex, is that you? Just give
me something backstage so I know it's you, Alex McQueen. Tell me something that I know
it's you. Oh my god. I have form bombers under your name.
We're gonna let you queen up here right now. And Alex, Alex, you know there's new rules
Miska's never experienced
Yeah, Alison's quite rude. I mean he was on I think he told my friend. I have a friend
She's like a little a little bit of an older lady, but she's like a like a psychic and she's has a nice show
And she's came on is like, oh you're eating you just call it or he's been so rude to some people and
You know, I have to be careful, but Alex prove it to you. I just need to prove it's him
He's not typing. I don't believe it's you and so you do something
Yeah
Yeah, no, it's great. He get too crazy. But I mean, he was trying to like some of the
things that he would say were pretty outrageous, you know, all they do.
Oh my god, would he had to fuck it? Oh, he dressed up and was doing his little dance on the chair and shit like oh my god
I just sit back and put it on the team. He saw him do that. I saw him came up only one time
He looked like a young Ray Leota. Oh, Jesus Christ. He had his cop shirt on
Yeah, he's got all the all the toys and I was like
I wish there's a way to... It was funny itself
If I let him up and it's like not him you're gonna get bomb bombed. Yeah, you don't put up a banner
He'll say the n word a bunch of time. Oh, hold on. Hold on. It's him. It's him. I know it's him
Alex
Alex you're on the air go ahead. I know it's you now
Oh, it's him Alex
What is Canada dry have a like something that looks like a girl next to him
You got a girlfriend. Yeah
I've been a girlfriend for six years get out of here. I told you Alex
No, but we didn't believe you dick. I we started thinking you were gay
When you first came up here, bro, you had it made everybody thought you were the hottest shit
I'm like, all right. He's a little good looking whatever besides me
They were like, he's so hot. He's so hot. I can't enjoy then you went crazy and I show up with a woman
And next
You're next on my on my list. Yeah
Why did you disappear
I have my own psyche. I love you. Oh, oh, I got this fucking cigarette voice
And then you just ran away for ten years and now you're back
You abandoned psyche
Why I walked away and why though was it me wasn't me
I'm not gonna get involved in that bullshit
This is the free cops. She didn't like the free cops going on
Fucking be discriminant all the time. Nobody can get a word in there twice
Fucking I know it's worse right now. I'm tripping
I'm tripping psyche and staying out of space
Canada dry has a girlfriend and acts as back. I'm tripping
Yeah, I mean I'm gonna take also done my uh my background right no Canada you have to give her a kiss cuz I don't believe it's real
It's AI right
No burning give her a smooch pinch your cheek. I know oh my god. It's real Jesus. Well, it's real
I am actually
Oh my another smooch
My alien alien right there. I know man in charge. He's pretty bad. I like the color
Thank you. This was a gift from one of my
Subscribers
What's that? What's what's that one picture?
It's very nice. Yes, it is
Very proud of that like I
Like it where people give you shit for it and you defend. I know it. I know
You see ice supporting the whole planet, I know it is great the best
You motherfuckers
So for me I like up the whole fucking planet, man
No, uh-uh, it's over
If I got to work at 60 years of age to take care of the old man
Fuck that shit. Didn't they go out there and work just like I did when he was raising his kids
60 years of age working, that's crazy.
Well, no, I want to turn 60, I didn't start on it, baby, so.
I do have a different habit.
The United States is good if you get into its system, so it works this way.
You work your whole life to about 60, you retire, and all the taxes that you pay through
Money you acquired through your working life. It makes sense. You understand all the country does that shit
Like listen, you come here. You have a good life. You work. You pay taxes
When you start getting old you can retire and then we'll take care of you. I got five more years to work
It's called the fucking
So if you don't work, you don't get no money at the end of your life. Yeah, you do
That's why people become homeless like why you homeless because I didn't work. I have no fucking, you know
You have to put in to get back
Yes
Yeah, you got a gift to get yeah, correct. You have to play to exactly
You're not just gonna lift you for free and then get old and be like oh when my home is like a so
You didn't work a day in your life
If you did you were collected fucking you know
your pension
It's a good system it works it works
People get a lot of money when they retire from their fucking
It all depends on what you gave through life what you get back
I know people that own companies, right big companies
and then retire and now they got the whole shit set so security just to check how many cars are we
boom boom three grand a month three or four grand a month boom boom boom boom
for the rest of the life it all depends where you give back what you do and that's what you're gonna get
If you don't do shit, you're gonna get a four hundred dollar a month social security. That's not gonna do shit
Or you can get four grains
The lowest you go but
You have to what do you can't live off that right now. What do you create there? We start on fucking all food every day
63 bands so I can register or might have passed inspection sticker
She's talking about inspection stickers my bad
um this little celebration for you got it the new star the new star of the show there you go guys
Katrina I was literally just thinking that when he said I appear like the wind I literally was going
to say like a fart and why is this girl how do you have a girl next to you
Thinking things like this. Hold on. Hold on. I want to know who this girl is and what she finds attractive
About you thinking about forts in the wind
I'll be fucking right now. It just
And you're like, I'm Katrina. You're right for time. I don't know, bro. I don't know
Canada does it
He's heart broke. All right. Look at psych. Obviously he lost his mind
Look at him for six years
What's this fucking mark? I
Just donated 10 members. I don't know. I don't know who got them but
I hope I got one vote because I'm not membership, you know, by we're again
Okay
You know I'm kidding dick. I mean because of the the hurtful
Name, you know you hurt me you hurt me Alex. I hurt you huh? Yeah, I hurt you. Oh my gosh
You hurt me dick, how did I hurt you?
I don't tell me how I hurt you because I didn't do anything to you hurt me
by
Well, I got a fucking list, but are you ready because you got time
You may have a two hours
You threw me away for those
Tell my everybody Christine damn
the
Well, yeah, whatever
No, no listen, I'm not talking about nobody. I'm so by you and me baby. All right, this is the drain it down to you and me
Nobody has none
With me and you and your princess Leia had phones
And what was over the sunglasses dick? Holy shit?
they do
Is that an alien next to you where the fuck are the cats? What's going on here, bro?
I mean the toilet's on right now
Cats are here the cats are fine. Alex. I don't see one cat around
Cool one cat bro. There's 30 cats in that room show me one
One got to meow meow come meow meow meow come to papa
Summons a cat, bro before I call fucking FBI
No, they love you but at the same time they just hurry up and get it over with dick
you know they said different you ever seen page you ever seen page prairie
wins hold the cat the cats like they're like little babies like they don't want
to like go away they're like national inter like these cats are streaming
Alex, go fuck yourself, okay, and you're banned again, okay?
Third strike, Alex, go fuck yourself, okay, Alex?
It's a source of that.
I told you to shut the fuck up about it,
and you kept going, okay?
So, Alex, you're banned, okay?
I don't care.
I don't like you anymore, okay?
Go, kick that a studio, bye.
I have no sense of humor about it right now, Alex.
What's happening?
You can actually talk to me, Alex,
and find out what's happening,
but since you just went and do that right now,
it's not the time, okay?
Nope, not the time, Alex.
You never know how to read a room, that's your problem, okay?
Okay.
And the reason you got kicked off is because you called Page the C-word, okay?
And Page is not a C-word, okay?
And Page would never say anything like that to you.
You're a fucking asshole, Alex.
Bye.
Not the time, Alex.
Yeah, Alex.
Well, yeah, you don't maybe you don't know what happened either Canada drive, but I'm not going to repeat it either but it's like
Yeah, it's not good it's not good the pages is sweet. All right. She don't do nobody wrong
Oh, you know shit. No, she never did. Yeah, she's into just being friends and talking and you know time
What did time say there?
time said uh, I've never known page
Like the drama much you know the drys girl know about how much she talks to page. I
don't know
Quite a lot. Hey guys probably yeah, I guess I don't couple times a day
Really that needy
I was curious about who Romeo cross is to because it was I don't like I don't like him saying even that comment
because I know like yellow is like means like low cow or something like that no they're calling me cold play
Oh shit. Yeah, I just like uh, yeah
There's been a lot of stuff going on guys and I'm I'm a little bit
Yeah, I had her number
Hey Vicky Vicky's there and Katrina. Halo. Okay. I
Do I mean I have made some new some new stuff. I don't know. Did you see my
new people in the chat compared to way back when I
You know, yeah
Mostly the
The ones that need the drama are in beaters now is ring
They cross you me or is it just a coincidence that they're saying I look like cold play
No, I don't know. I don't know what cold play looks like
I would say chicken Andy, but yeah, hopefully
Andy
Yeah, he does kind of look like chicken Andy, doesn't he? No, he's like a
No, I hate the name
No, not even
He's no, he's actually he's a he's a good-looking guy. I think he's an IPT or something like that
He's a chicken. He's chicken. He is a good-looking kid. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he is a good-looking kid
Yeah, I almost got to meet him
Okay
What's his name Boston whatever was on the I be the first one and
Then the guy died
Boston I was gonna get me a limo it was 75 bucks and grab a white limo and fucking go to Boston
You know and then I guess the kid overdosed to something
And I never got to collab with him
He was a good kid his name was Boston
Robertson
Boston Boston Robb was the guy from Survivor, I think
No, I'm not talking about TV. I don't want television. Okay. I'm talking about off the first RV
Okay, yeah, the RV stuff. Oh, Mr. Big Pipes is here. Hold on one second. Mr. Big Pipes.
I see Ghost in the tomb. Hey, what's up? I see Ghost. Hi, how are you? I'm doing well.
Everyone know Mr. Big Pipes? I remember. I know Tracy. Mr. Big Pipes. I've seen him.
I wanted to be in for a little while, but he's but he's back and not every time I ran into him in Jim Nick's
chat and
This guy came on there and started yelling at me
Oh man the concert she's been going to down there in Texas
I
Does Jim Nick really wear a diaper or is that a joke she makes
I heard her one day say I need to go put on my diaper and I didn't even want to ask if it was a joke
That's why I'm asking you guys cuz I genuinely didn't know if she was joking or not
Boy she was joking that time when she did it because I was watching that one too, but yeah
I would imagine some of the chemo and whatever medicine
Oh
That kid's real bad sick liver damage. Oh, wow. Yeah
Bad liver damage
Get fun one night because we were like kind of like
I started dancing for Mr. Big Pipes and then she started dance. Oh
Yeah, I'm about to get in trouble. I'm gonna shut up now, but yeah, this mr. Big Pipes
Mr. Big Pipes he ruined the freak off because you couldn't cam up and so it was just me
No, actually we went backstage and you started pushing boundaries and I was like I'm recording this just so you know
Did you record it right no then when I told you I was recording you back
No, I mean I showed as much as I show
What is Cliff's dick balled I
Don't know that I look like his dick balled. I don't even know what it is a BLD even a word
Yes, it is bald. It's like, you know, people are bald their head is dick bald like his bald dick. Like is he a is he a
Loser loser if you record I didn't show anything loser. All I did was lift you have a bald dick
I wiggle butt
With your princess lay your headphones
No, like thing that is it just in the context my dick bald it didn't
It didn't jive. It doesn't really make grammatical sense
In that context, no, I don't think bald is a word
Okay, I want to I want to show you the other the other video I made
Well go ahead
Okay, well before if I don't know if you're getting tired, but I want to show the other AI
Me in a video my girlfriend's girlfriend. Yeah, all you can see is her face. Yeah, play it
This is called to I need to start paying attention to the chat
I'm gonna take a quick a quick video and now this is considered as a commercial break. I'll be right back
of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight crowds came running just to see the flame
but envy was the price of fame and now he stands where the echoes fall with tarot in
hand hearing every call from praise to venom
Canada dredge it off, I'm sorry if you didn't like the Canada Dredge, but that can be creative too.
Let's go.
Hey, Velda.
Wow.
Do you want some proof of Raiders?
Okay, here we go.
Oh.
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, Susanna!
It was a D only a B minor and G and the break time was on F sharp minor to B.
Cecil plays banjo and guitar and keyboard and yeah he's been he grew up with bluegrass.
and
I'm gonna rent the goddamn rooms out and it's got a big old porch
Fuck I'll build a goddamn stage in the backyard put the old man and anybody wants to play in town
So remember guys, remember guys, remember guys, remember I'm in charge here and so don't forget to give me my, my, I need my flowers okay, and that's how I get everything, certain person, certain person.
Did I ever get that trailer issue resolved?
Tell me about it. I remember like something had. Oh is he talking about the RV about the rent the RV
I rented? Yeah, and he said it was like bad water or something. Yeah, that was for like the dude. I
don't know. I could have probably like pushed it, but dude, I still got it like I got that place
charged me another 500 bucks like the other week.
Frick, so it's just been monster like dealing with this stuff
Well, so the loser is you me or so, you know, who's the loser? Who's who keeps retracting every message like that?
I don't know. Oh, probably the loser. I like I wouldn't
Personally
Yeah, I'm up to block him because I don't like that I don't know is that you mean because they're like the nastiest person
Okay, but I would block on like from my own just so I don't have to stand but since I'm
Yeah, they trolling
I'm getting really annoyed by some behavior obscene chat
So I end up paying the guy I gave him 140 bucks for the for the dent in the bumper
But that's what I try to do
like he finally accepted it like he's like it took you to your shop and like he probably didn't get it fixed like I could have
put boiling water on it and fixed it I was just like hey dude like I don't know I was just like you know
it was a piece of plastic like yeah I got one of them F-150s I'm paying off $52,000 worth of truck
I got the one with the twin turbos coming off the exhaust
It's a six. I'm reading. Yes. I'm reading chat. I'm reading chat. I'm getting annoyed. I'm reading chat. Yeah
I have to
Who beaters doxing beta you're about to be guys if you dox pictures come on
I don't fucking care like some of it like most of these now I'm saying that when they're deleted messages is really nasty
Nasty stuff it's like just don't you know what if you don't want your if you don't want a record in the chat of what you say
Don't even say it like
Well, the thing is is we can still see it on stream yard side
Uh-huh. Yeah, even if they delete it you still see it on stream yard thread. Yeah, I'm gonna go back up and see what they were saying
Oh, yeah, it gets recorded
Just cuz you deleted just comes out of them chat. That's it
On on the stream yard side all that is being recorded so when it sits in your memory and
Stream yards so doesn't a complete chat
I'm looking at the messages and you're saying R.I.P. like everyone was saying about me yesterday.
No, no, no, no, no. Loser, I knew it. I was about to mod you, too.
The wheel quit the chair.
Oh, not anymore. Now you're banned because I can tell they were saying that in previous chats about me all day.
So, I'm not like that. So, hi.
Okay. And plus don't call Mr. Big Pipes. You're not supposed to harass Mr. Big Pipes.
Now you're fine rameo cross. Okay, I know you're a bit
I can trade my camper in or find a piece of property and put a roof over it
Um, I would have let Panna on the panel, but I didn't see never came up
He was just in the chat and I don't think he tried to come on panel. I post the link and
He never came up. I did not because I because now stream art puts a message when someone comes in the studio
So I really will always see it and so he didn't I didn't buy them up
But hopefully maybe this I come by something
Yeah, thanks to you ever said they like my harmonica
I didn't hear you harmonica
Yeah
Okay, oh yeah, I'm gonna take a nicotine so I could
Yes, I can hear you yes
I'm not I can barely see the chat because now I got all distracted
Some other what'd you do you weird in the chat?
By his mods, please
Because there's a lot of people that aren't mods in the chat right now.
Come on, okay so yeah, that person is okay.
I just have to be more careful with the, especially the show too.
I would have let him up, Gotti, but I don't know.
Hold on, okay.
Yeah, I'm not gonna, I'm gonna relax about it.
Okay, oh shit.
Hold on.
Okay.
Um, I don't know who you are Ramio, but I just have a bad feeling I just go with my gut feeling about people sometimes and
I'm gonna do it this time
Well, I think you know, it's good. He was he was he was a get-and-beat-his-chat talking shit about me like a lot of these people
That's what they do over there
It's drama central
So Tracy you you've spent some time with Jose Sanders I've
He's been the night or I've spent two weeks two weekends with him. I
How'd you do that? I was off the fucking recliner and gonna hit him
And he thought that we're gonna ball. I almost smacked him in the back of the fucking head
Until he I saw him for the retard he was
And then I let him stay one more night
And he wanted to stay a week and I said the fuck you are and I took him to man's bike and dropped him off the first
Truck you can see that happen. Well, I like I cut him. You gotta cut them off. You have your early
And then you did this part. He did he did do one day after he left I found pizza crust under the fucking couch
I'm like, dude
That's why nobody lets him go any farther than the garage I didn't find until like months later. I'm like, how the fuck did this? Oh
I made him his plate I cut his meat up so I wouldn't even give him a damn steak knife
He fucking typed me great, and I'm like no way I fucking raped your little eyes
Tracy he'd say like a great word great. Yeah, great. Yeah
And I don't say this is a hard one. No, well, and then I was like
You slept up at Cecil's house
Cecil had to make him take a shower
Oh, I thought he wouldn't actually the first time he did he put his dirty clothes back on and fucking stop
could have ran away I
Thought like I had fun with him person like I thought like I could see how he can be like you just got a set boundaries
Really quick. No, and I told him I said look I said, you know, don't live stream up there
And on his last day
I fucking I woke up at 9 30. He's up there. Well, he can see so up fucking live streaming playing all his guitars and banjoes and shit
And I'm fucking down here and I run up there and I'm like no I said, that's it
You've got to go and then he took $20 and and some needles from fucking
Cecil come down and got another $20 and a half of my weed
Without telling me I said that you all sat because he had just come from Cecil and
He didn't say nothing. So I didn't think Cecil give him anything. So I gave it to him
So my fucking double dick just out of 40 bucks and more weedles than we had when we got done. Oh
Yeah, that little bastard and I bought one of those stoves
Let him borrow money off of my card
On Amazon and it was two hundred eighty nine dollars, and I know he gets his fucking he gets an idiot check
Okay, as parents are black the ones that adopted him there in the military or
retired military is
You know father is he told me his parents were like mega millionaires
No, they're middle-class
Nonsmokers
Work their asses off
And he won't respect anything
He's not allowed back at the house because he went down in the basement and got shit-faced for a couple of days and
spraying fucking Lysol or whatever
Smoking cigarettes down there thinking they weren't gonna smell it and then on smokers
No, it was crazy and they told him said don't come back
But they're the ones that are to pay you through its Walmart cards. He gets check on the first and then on the 15th
I don't know
He tells everybody he don't get nothing that he's desolate, but when he gets in hard times
His parents fucking I've known him for
Hold on. He's been on YouTube
Okay, he showed up in the slabs when I was
God, this is six seven eight years ago. Yeah, I first encountered him probably like four or five years ago
That's it. No, he got gone. We
Why you know, I met him on YouTube. He was driving
He had his license and he went with his uncle to drop off a pickup truck
down nearby Nile and
He went to the slabs and he got accused of stealing something and he started a YouTube channel
And then all of a sudden he got gone for two weeks.
He still to this day hasn't told where he ended up for two weeks.
All of a sudden I'm talking to his parents and we're trying to find him.
And I'm a YouTuber so I'm scanning the place.
Me and Stellar are scanning it.
Trying to find him two weeks later he showed back up on YouTube.
To this day he won't say what the hell happened to him.
I'd imagine he got accosted for two weeks.
Yeah, he got into some shit down there by slabs, but that's when I started to follow on him
Shit, I had one burn up on me on a fucking live stream burnt to death
That one was a hard one
He was in the shed fucking with gasoline all of a sudden the little shit went up in flames and that was Joe
I had fun with him. I would chill with him again. Yeah, if I was the guy and I didn't have any responsibilities
But as far as putting him in a normal environment, he pushes the left. He's a wrecking ball
No, he wants to see how far he can push you before you're gonna hit him
I don't know. He definitely does. He definitely does. I think you can tell it is like
Yeah, like push me towards like snapping and he like he knows I'm like
Cecil asked him to go pass him a wrench he says look the truck needs an oil
change before we take you you know all the way down route to or down the mass
pike and he wouldn't even hand Cecil a wrench he said I don't do those things so
I sit next to him on the couch and I said Cecil's asking you to help him do the
oil change all you have to do is hand him the wrench the tools
and he wouldn't fucking do it.
He said, I won't do it.
I mean, that's how lazy he is.
He wouldn't even help with the fucking answers
on a fucking wrench.
I was in the American stuff.
He rusted, but I got mad respect for him
for how much he rusted out in the wilderness.
Like, that's insane.
What? Okay. Katrina, Katrina, don't test me.
Do you know when he sets up his fucking tent inside fucking Stella's trailer to make it
look like he was living outside when he was all he was was at the end of Stella's trailer
in the fucking back bedroom in a tent? I mean, I've seen the guy, like, I've smelled
the guy. He doesn't care. He can't.
Ejaculate and when he does oh my god, I didn't need it. I didn't need to know. Oh, do you not know Sarah Bean?
I've heard all about the drama and stuff, but oh
When he went through a trailer. Yeah, I'm about to end because I'm really pissed off by certain why
Because I'm just like with being taped and stuff like that. Yeah
No, I
Can tell who they are. I know they are and I'm not like it. Hey, you let them get to you
I mean, I was just on your mix and like salmon came on there like talking trash
I was left. Do you know Sam? If you know who's a do you know Sam?
No, no Cadillac Sam
No, no, okay. Is that his name on youtuber? Uh, it was
now it's
Think it's Sam Spandler. I don't know but he was another youtuber that started off down there. It's lab cities
We had a whole community and gone shown that's under instant. I don't know. It's just like
Still in touch with each other after eight years, let's say
I don't trust you. I don't trust you Bader. I don't trust you Bader. Oh my god. I
Watched I watched Bader's show by the way, so I know I really but I think he has I think he's like 10 people in this chat right now
I'm not even you
No, I don't care if they do. I mean you're allowed to get credit for that
It's true. You can strike it down. It's your trolling me right? Yeah
No, no, I'm not gonna. I don't strike anybody for streaming. Hello
No, it's it's publicity. I feel like
Well, sometimes I'm gonna be bad, but no, no, I uh, yeah, I'm probably
How many fucking people you block now?
Oh, oh, there's like a hundred people blocked tonight, but it's like that's why
Probably I
I already blocked anybody, but it's like no people can I'm doxing people came in attacking. No, that's not cool
That'll get you in trouble
Right, right, right. And this is yeah. Yeah, and YouTube holds your chat responsible
Unless you hide the chat when you go too long
Yeah
People can report your chat for hate speech. Yeah
Fucking people just annoying me and it's like I don't it's like they're really pissing you off smoke a joint
So they've been smoking with roaches a lot of weed
I wish I had some, I wish I had some.
I know.
But it's like, I can't get some, but it's like,
and now it's been closed for several hours.
Because it's like...
It's fucking after 12 where you're at.
It's almost 12.30 where you're at.
It is 12.26.
One, two, two, six.
Because it's 3.26 here.
Okay, I'm just gonna try to ignore the chat mods. Keep an eye on things
I know
Because it's not even like necessarily what they're saying it's like others saying
Just to get the reaction idea. Well, they're a reaction the reactions and they're gonna get out of the chat because it's
But they've got a hundred million fucking emails
Probably unlimited, but still
I can start playing whack-a-mole
But you're gonna walk especially gaudi gaudi don't
Don't don't start with me, Gotti. I'll start
Okay, I'm in the stream, but thank you guys. Thank you so much
Thanks for having me on
Gotti's harassing me about eating and stuff like that. I sat here eating a TV dinner and I have to have a sandwich left and
and
Are you trying to type? Type in your blocked?
Yeah, I'm blocked in the chat.
Oh my god, hold on.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I am serious.
Yeah, are you sure maybe you're just
Put the word giggles across
Yeah, I already do
Yeah
Anybody block
I don't know. I don't know.
Yeah
And
I have to like I mean I have to do like a kind of like
Orientation or something for people that I mod because it won't help
I don't trust you, God, you're about to be unmodded right now.
I'm gonna really piss off with you two, okay?
Don't fucking play with me, guys, okay?
Okay, Dingle is out of here, that's God.
Dingle is God, I know who Dingle is,
and God, you're almost out of here.
Guys, guys, I'm not gonna play with you right now.
Yes, oh really, really, you're unmodded.
I don't like what's going on in the chat, I mean I'm ending it because I love you though,
people are just playing with me, I don't like it, like RG, is that what you're testing
Okay, stay turned as banned, okay?
As banned, dark helmet is banned.
Anyone telling me to relax is gonna be banned, okay?
Don't tell me to relax.
I'm saying nothing right now.
If you smoke, don't pass it.
I hope I'll ban everybody.
Got it?
Now you're hit it.
Okay, got it, bye.
Bye.
Bye, everybody from CFCC is banned.
He's coming back.
You ruin it for everybody who got him, okay?
Oh, God, he's coming up.
No, he's not, because he's banned.
Oh, he's banned.
I ain't lying.
Oh, he's annoying me because if you guys you understand, this is my this is my show
So if you're annoying me, if you're trying to annoy me, I'm not gonna fucking put up with it. You're gonna be gone right away
Like RG
I'm sorry, that was an accident. Oh my god
Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do
My chat
This just fall that's right. It's just I did I did the spike on you. Yeah
Yeah, they did you know you be you be keep you be keep on tagging keep on tagging us. Okay. I love it. I love it
Black RG, you know, okay, so I mean I try to tell you I try to tell you to stop you know strikes strike strike strike
Okay, bye guys bye bye guys
Tracy I told you I told you I was ready to go. Yes. I love you guys
They're they're upsetting me and they're now they're antagonizing me and so okay
I'm gonna go to bed. It's straight. I love you. I love you Tracy. I love you Tracy
I got a thing rage
Okay, there you go, okay goodbye guys
Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never
The unexpected.
psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand the angels are dancing torchlight in
hand let's start the show
okay i'll say i'll say um for a few minutes because jamey's here but you i'm like having a really
It's like just don't talk to me like that way
Okay, let's go. Hey Joey. Thank you. It's like hey, I don't know if you're gay or not
But that intro song is definitely gay, but I appreciate you man. You're a good
Not in the mood.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Hello?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to save for a few minutes
because Jamie's here.
Jamie Rose is here.
But yeah, I think you can walk up.
No, you can't you can totally say I'm like I just
It's like I'm just being like I could I could tell like there's somebody on like multiple alts and then people are just like
Basically, just like kind of sneak sneak to see me
Yeah, I don't like I don't like it. I know some of the things I was saying too. It's like yeah for years
And it's like, I'm not dumb.
It's like, I'm really sensitive to energy
and I'm a little bit sensitive right now.
So I do, I mean, if I got somebody, you know,
on the wrong, but I'm kind of feeling like, you know,
I shouldn't, I should be very careful
what I trust right now.
I think I'm being way too trusting with some people.
Okay, is like, God, he's gonna say laugh at me
and like whatever he was saying,
like he was just, he was saying,
Weird shit too. I don't I just I just if I get that if I get that icky feeling
I'm just gonna go like trust trust it, right?
Yeah, I don't want and I'm not gonna I'm not gonna deal with like them slowly like just like wearing down on me
Yeah, it's like most most
Most of them are not even
And you guys feel like subs on you know, and you'll get the watch time. Yeah, I might do that. I might do that
That was I was down to I was down to like mod people, but it's like I just need to make sure that they're
Real and a lot of these people have already said that they're not
My friend, right? So I'm just being careful. I don't I don't know it's like
Mr. Big Pipes is not very like I don't know if you heard what happened yesterday, but it's like not very
I'm actually pretty cool and it's like
And I and like I said, I was like, I'll give people one more chance, but it's like I
Said one more chance. It's like it's like if you're gonna fuck that up. You're not the you're not the yeah
Thank you, but thank you Bella and some of these people
And slowly just kind of like, just keep tap, tap, tap.
And I'm like, hey, you know, just chill.
Stop talking to me like I'm like, like, oh, relax, relax.
Don't tell me to relax on my own show.
I don't like to be told to relax.
That you can't take a joke.
It's like, what?
I can't right now.
This is don't test me.
Not in the mood.
I'm not in the mood to talk about I'm gay because whatever.
I'm gay.
What, you're a problem?
You got a problem with it?
Not you, but I'm talking.
There are people with problems with it.
Together, I'm here, I'm getting,
honestly, tagging gay, gay, I know you, I know you don't.
I got tagged in as gay, H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T,
post the other night.
And then the next day, those same people from that chat
came in here, came in betas, and then
started this whole thing where they're saying really bad things about me and bringing my cats into it and stuff and
I do not appreciate a lot of stuff. And so some of it wasn't test to see like
Yeah, psyche super gay. Okay, whoever that is is like, you know another example of
Somebody that's gonna be just hidden immediately
Um, yeah, don't guys, this is my show. Do you understand? It's like you're in my house on this show
So it's like you're not gonna go in a house and just like go in a little corner and smoke cigarettes put them out in the
Plants and like laugh with your friends and nor me or make fun of me. Okay, I'm not gonna have it anymore
I'm gonna have people I know in this chat. Okay, but I have such good people here and
I'm I really have an eye on people and don't yeah, don't say all you mean you guys you're just
Pointing yourself out for being a hidden if you like say that and so it's like kind of like dumb
Like you're doing on purpose. If you want to be hidden on purpose. What are you doing?
Just shut up like people that are saying this shit
I'm saying for Jamie Rose is all this and for the nice people here. Thank you, Belle
Belle though. Okay, Jamie Rose. Yay. Okay
Hi
Welcome Jamie
How are you doing? Can you hear me? Okay? I hear you. I hear you
And have been a little bit of a difficult
week lately and
You know, it's been a little pretty it was pretty rough earlier tonight, too
And in this this birch out and Alex you're not coming up Alex. You're not Alex
the fake cop
Tell me about your week when you say it wasn't so great, because I've been gone for a lot
minutes.
Well, there's another mutual friend of ours probably and who also a streamer late at night
started just harping on me about, I had to back on my table.
They said it was cat shit.
And then it turned into like her whole chat was like,
oh my God, there's cat shit everywhere.
I mean, it's like, it just sort of,
like the whole entire chat started like screaming
about it and saying, I'll call on the ASPCA
and I'm abusing my cats.
I let my cats be eaten by coyotes and be hit by cars
and I don't take care of them.
And it's just like really, and then it's like, you know,
I don't feel like anybody like many people had my back and some people did and like a lot of people here did
Something happened to King Cobra
Just King Cobra, I don't know that that streamer
Yeah, so I just wanted to let everyone know about cobes in case they hadn't heard have a safe night everyone
Gotta what?
Uh, it says I just wanted to let everyone know about Coby's in case they hadn't heard have a safe night everyone
We're talking about King Cobra JCS. Yeah, I know he is but
What happened? Did we know what happened to him or anything?
Yeah, I'm trying to change so then I'm trying to like and it's like and then a lot of people get so like I've been just so
Harping on me for all these different things. I mean, I got I mean, it's just like there's so there's so much
It's been said that it's like hurt purple and everything from being told every day of HIV and all this kind of stuff
And then doxing a million times my chat tonight
Who is it? What do you mean who is it like who's King Cobra? He's a streamer. He's a
Autistic man who is obsessed with Ozzy Ozzy Al's foreign recipes
There's a great heredyne video if you type in King Cobra heredy, I would recommend that
But I mean, I hope he's not dead I don't wish death on anyone
If you don't know what happened to them, then we can just skip that.
So people were upset with you because they saw some cat shit or something?
No, they didn't.
They taught tobacco.
I had some tobacco on my table, right?
It's like, I can't communicate with this.
And then it was from the night before that, I got tagged in this, or I didn't get tagged,
So the thing popped up and it said, I'll spell it out H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T dot gay.
And that was some websites, I just had a weird feeling about it.
And so I sent it to beat I was like, look at this, look at this like weird website.
It's like a go daddy, like temporary website that was put up.
And I was just like.
Um, let's see. Hold on.
I don't mean it's in the name.
Yeah, it's in the name.
Words, maybe band, boo boo.
Okay, anyway, I don't know what to think about this thing.
But anyway, um, so,
but it went from like, you know,
so this person named Kiss My Cheeks,
and then Eldo came in like harassing me,
saying over and over.
Yeah, and also then it's like the night before that it was Bronzeberg and it's just like and yeah, so here's nothing
I'll give you the real uh run down here. Yeah. Oh, yeah, it says he passed away. Wow
For real he did
So he is found and responsive in his home according to reports from kiwi farms. Well
That was
Then in a guy I'm hassling that's a glassblower guy. It was like a long-time mod of his and
Covertos come into his discordance
Bound to happen yet
Like I think gout on his foot the worst diet, and I don't need to laugh the worst diet. I've ever seen
drinks like a lot of major addictions
Yeah, I'm not surprised
tough duster and stuff
recipes, but yeah that that website you were talking about
Yeah, it's in the name that it's probably not gonna be the best site
Yeah, but what I was thinking about the website is that the people that were like Eldo and
this person kissed my cheeks came in and started this whole stuff, and then they're on that
Discord server.
Just coincidentally that I had pointed at the Discord server that that website had come
out of, that I share with Vita just because I had a weird feeling about, I was like, we
Okay, now I remember what I was going to tell you so the what you're getting is the runoff from people like I guess we would call trolls being bored because they're normal people they interact with are not, you know, it's just boring.
Right.
Well, I would like say a lot of overspill because then it like came on like all this
doxing and like tonight, not even saying it's me, but it's phone numbers, addresses, names,
coming in saying just accused, you know, great, great best, you know, all the, I mean, just
really, and then, you know, my cats are like, you know,
just don't fuck with my cats and bring my cats into this,
but it's like, it just turned into,
it was not even like just the trolls,
because there was a couple of trolls, right?
But it turned into like, all these people like,
just turned into like this mass,
everybody started bullying.
And even like, you know,
Like I came in there like so in such a good mood like before and like such good things happening and it's like and
And then it's like everything turned is like even
Friends of mine with apparently black or RG. Yes, you're gonna come in really good is coming right back in RG
Well, I just knew but then he started and he started saying he's like, well, what do you know?
He's like, you're not that perceptive or whatever when I was like saying, oh, there's I know that
I know who the person is that under 10 also right like RG and that perceptive, okay?
So then he started and then he said, oh, we'll calm down or whatever. I don't want to be told to calm down
I I know that it's like, okay. I'm giving me the fucking fuel but it's like maybe it's okay
I mean, I'm gonna I'm banned everybody anyway, but
It's like it's just not the right time to like
Kid around with me. I'm not in the kidding mood. It's like I'm just like
I'm really
hurt and
annoyed and then it's like
Can't even I don't care. Okay, didn't it is okay?
I don't wanna hear it, I don't, guys, this is my show, okay?
Don't tell me how to feel or what to do.
Please, stop it, okay?
I will fucking ban everybody in this chat, okay?
I don't care, I'll have Jamie Rose and Jamie's Cowboys
and they're the only two people I ever talk to again, okay?
Don't fucking play with me right now.
It's been, Jamie Rose, it has been like constant,
it's like,
like the fucking weirdest, weirdest fucking shit.
And it's like, they're not kidding around with me,
they're fucking playing with me, okay?
And they're trolling me, and yeah.
And Erby, yeah, thank you.
Yeah, they're here as a guest,
and I told everybody earlier, I was like,
you know, this is my show, I'm the captain of the ship.
We're gonna be here at least like, respect me.
Oh, okay, so, okay.
I'm trying to have you see more reason.
I don't need to be told this, okay?
I understand what's going on, thing that is.
You're annoying me by fucking telling me what to do
and how to think, okay?
I understand, okay?
Don't tell me, don't tell me, okay?
I already know.
How about just like respect me and be nice, okay?
Well, but that's a really annoyed it is
I get that you're annoyed and it does
Sometimes you know on the internet who's playing that awful guitar. This is mr. Big Pipe's
Okay
It's like I watched this a comedy special the other day
Oh was was it Kevin Nealon like an old Kevin Nealon skit and there was just like some random like
Guitar playing in the background. It's very awkward. It's kind of feels like that
But I'm psych psyche is it psych or psyche?
I mean either one is fine. All right
Well, psyche is a goddess name and it's called psyche awakens because it's kind of like a reference to Q
But actually but but psyche. I like I like psyche
Yeah, mr. Big Pipes, it's not the time. It's not the time mr. Big Pipes, and I'll let black herbs you on and you can tell me
Give me a piece of my yeah, okay one second
And I like you mr. Big Pipes come back later, okay?
Not the time
Hello, how are you?
I've been better. Thank you for getting rid of Big Pipes before I got up here that guy gets a light nerve
like I'm telling you I'm not that crazy I understand like what a noise I didn't say you were crazy
I just got here and you seemed upset that's all I was just playing around but you know what's been
happening RJ did you see that? I don't know I just got I just like I took my sleep hours are weird
so I woke up and you were all upset and I gotta say more often than not I come up here and you're
really upset so it doesn't seem like you're enjoying this very much
Right, I'm not. I'm about to quit doing the show.
Okay, it's like I'm on my last fucking straw with it.
It's like, it's becoming like cruel.
It's becoming just like sadistic.
It's becoming...
soul, soul murder.
You can't let it get to you though.
Because it's even beat it, beat it's doing the same,
beat it's doing it too.
It's like, and it's like, it's fucking,
and then I know somebody, I know this,
I get told things, so I know who's here under Ken Alts
with Gotti and all these people.
It's like, just constant troll to troll.
I'm trying to like, I had such a good night,
most of the night, I was having such a good night.
And I have to like make fun of my,
like every little thing, just saying these little things.
energy of it and so I'm not gonna put up with it and it's like and I try to warn
people and they're not listening and it's frustrating because it's like they're
shouting themselves out. A few days ago I suggested that you take it maybe a few
days off and maybe come back with a fresh out pair eyes at all this. Please don't
make suggestions. I'm just saying a few days ago I said that do it do what you
So, did you hear, uh, have you heard, uh, did you know about Jimmy's new girlfriend?
No, Miss Janet?
Yeah.
I mean, for real.
They're official now.
Tell them, I love you.
This is his first girlfriend, Jamie, like his first real girlfriend.
Have they met in person?
No, they're going to though
If there's any woman who will sleep on his cot and bang him surrounded by his bottles, it's Janet
Makes me so happy
That that would happen
It does it makes me so happy
Like I could quit trolling Jimmy now after three years
because he's gonna fall in love. She mentions Rob Rack every day, every fucking day she
talks about the guy in front of Jimmy. I mean, she has to. There's still something
where she's a narcissist. She's insane. She's an insane person. Well, normally I wouldn't
talk shit about her, but she's talked shit about me and all the time.
Especially now she she's very threatened by you by the way. Oh, yeah. He can't say Jamie
the dev the dev was up on
So just yesterday talking about you because that's what the dev does. Yeah, Jimmy like he was
He was like no no the past at the past and I don't be stinkin the hoods in a low
Then he stopped everything and started playing no ordinary love
Dude, I shit my pants laughing that's a perfect song which is very unlike Jimmy
You could never be a perfect
No, he's playing all these playing like all different types of he's opening instead of with gacer songs like fucking love songs from the 60s
Like it's unreal
But he won't admit to everyone that that's his girlfriend Janet will though. It's funny
Well, I did see something the other day because I haven't been on you know, anywhere on any
You know, I went off and got married or some shit, right? I did I did Jesus Christ. I thought
I'm happy. Well, I'm glad you're happy. Thank you
Okay
But you know Jimmy he just
Hmm
He will he just is so delusional
That's his issue. He has this channel. It's not much better
I was gonna tell you that the other day I didn't see this like clip I think it was from a
Groovy Janet
It's great, it's a great channel
Yeah, you're having fun. I didn't even know you were watching my streams. That's good to know
Yeah, like here and there if I can
You give me update. It's not Marty's
I miss the guy I do
Well, yeah, he's he was very funny and
You're saying Coby's made of past that's kind of a fucking bummer
I heard that, but what I was going to say is that it was Jimmy saying that Janet's not a looker.
Janet's not a looker.
Oh, that was that. You know what that clip came from?
When you first brought Rob Racks around trying to get, he was all pissed off.
He said he looked like someone from, uh, the fuck is that card there that video gives?
Yeah, maybe laugh. I found that someone found that clip for me, and I had to fucking post
That was one of my main missions my main goal was like let me bring
Rob rack and Jimmy together because they are so similar
I'm a mod over at Rob. I like Rob. Rob's fucking hilarious. I love Rob. He takes my range way
I'm bagging for it. I haven't brought you up over there yet, but he lets me get in all types of trouble. I love it
No, he lets me get all types of shit. He likes me. It's uh, it's been fun
He's very fun. Yeah
He's like Jimmy if Jimmy had a better personality. It was you know more clever and more funny
So what else would Jimmy he's been to lame Jen is
She's cocking them every chance she can she's getting between like his little inner circle like she hates scam
Because scam docks her and like her entire family
And no one like Scambo. Well, no, yeah, that's a fair point
That's a whiny bitch. He's whining
And he's just a shitty parent
Yeah, he's an awful parent
You know the kids the kids want cereal or something he's he's too busy sucking off groovy Jimmy to attend to his kids needs
It's fucking weird
that's what she does
she fucking latches on she gets her hooks in and she already has done that and she's just gonna tear this dude's life apart
I'm gonna laugh
i'm gonna laugh that's the type of woman she is dude she's insane she's a fucking untreated bipolar
you know and she's a narcissist and jimmy has never had a girlfriend this is his first this is
I definitely would love to watch it.
Ugh.
Just unraveling.
The groove, it's so hard to watch.
It's so fucking hard to watch.
Well, there is no groove, you know.
Mookie, try to bring it back, revive it.
But that wouldn't happen.
No.
Because Jimmy won't do it.
Well, that and Cyber had to get involved and fuck everything up.
But he's down like if he streams at night, which he does most of the time. He's down. He was 17 viewers max
Viewers this dude should be at like 300 200 at this point if not more
Janet who brags about how she makes and breaks YouTube channels streams the seven every day
And her little simp Irby is floating around here somewhere. That's another weirdo
Who?
Erby, I don't he's just a weird disabled guy who like moles for fucking Janet. Hmm. She has a whole bunch of weirdos that surround her
It's all weird. It's been a lot of fun though. Jenna hates my fucking Gus
Janet brought my love back for the game because I was getting really bored of Jimmy like really fucking bored
And I didn't, you know, I was like, you know, maybe I should just stop and then Janet came fucking
Came into my life. Now. I love it again
So yeah, like I said, there's a new horse in town
Yeah
Because I...
So it made a Mr. Ed parody.
I can't believe I'm talking horse references with Jamie Rose. No effect.
Yeah, go to that. You know, I'm your plug.
But so it made a picture of her with like the Mr. Ed song theme in the background.
I saw it.
Because his teeth is really funny.
I saw it. Great work.
You can see it.
I did. I did.
I appreciate it. It was it's all very funny everything that um you and uh oh my god crowed
crowed yeah it's hilarious yeah crow is trying to find this this tea he'll be back soon i'm sure
we still want that jimmy roe's interview by the way if you're willing to tell all
are you willing to tell all the i don't want no standardized version of it
You know it kind of
Okay, sure. Well, you do it on our stream that Jimmy will listen although. He's so fucking fancy fanciful right now with Janet
You know, he's
The nigga love
Yes, like with a broad that is banged nearly half a black YouTube
Well, Janet has a kid that's older than Jimmy
Oh, well, he's like a death retard kid. I know that
Why was I being a little blunt a little crass
This one he is
You want it Marty wouldn't put it any differently, I don't think you come with every
It's the truth.
So I can't like, I just, I mean, would I say it?
I'm not sure.
I like, but which is to hear it, it's, yeah, it's right there.
So Memphis says, Janet is just playing him.
I don't know, man.
She's very bipolar.
She falls in love easily.
She does bring up Rob rack an awful lot like
But I you know Rob and I
Like we have each other's numbers. So the time that uh, she crashed out with Bronzeberg. I
Immediately bronze bronze didn't even do anything
What would you say? I don't think bronze did anything. I like Bronzeberg. He's pretty good dude. He seems to be anyways
Yeah, he's he's always been nice to me, but no he sent me a clip of